909814791153356801;2017-09-18 16:22:04;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Today in Atrocities of Photoshop #datneck https://t.co/Xy8BWOQqss;[('Atrocities', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('of', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Photoshop', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814797671247872;2017-09-18 16:22:05;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;CNt stop listening to adult jazz;[('CNt', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814799940423687;2017-09-18 16:22:06;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;"@theswordcom Why do I have ""Little Respect (If Any) For Porn Actors, Especially Black Ones""?https://t.co/NMmD8VtuVn";[('Little', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Respect', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Especially', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Black', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ones', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814800015912960;2017-09-18 16:22:06;Croton-on-Hudson, NY;41.251326;-73.8972405;The walls are missing so many games. Like damn I though the mall's Wii section was bad, I had no idea;"[(""mall's"", 'MISC'), ('Wii', 'MISC')]"
909814803887247360;2017-09-18 16:22:07;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;The Game of Thrones/Harry Potter crossover we all needed. https://t.co/yieJ2JfRGW;[('Game', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('of', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Thrones', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Harry', 'PERSON'), ('Potter', 'PERSON')]
909814833150873600;2017-09-18 16:22:14;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;There is no job security Charles. #Ballers;[('Charles', 'PERSON')]
909814832911675392;2017-09-18 16:22:14;Manhattan, NY;40.7403518;-74.0084352;About-last night at boom boom room with this beauties abie_jammeh  rocking her Ngor shorts… https://t.co/pNRU5VlYOz;[('Ngor', 'PERSON')]
909814834753044480;2017-09-18 16:22:14;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Toxie's Musical in UK #westend  Pls join Toxie & moi Oct2 https://t.co/pq1j2u8LoF https://t.co/QZftyU9SPQ;[('UK', 'LOCATION'), ('Toxie', 'PERSON')]
909814840025341952;2017-09-18 16:22:16;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;I think the president should be Cecily Tyson, but Ang can be VP https://t.co/OIT7uLnwhQ;[('Cecily', 'PERSON'), ('Tyson', 'PERSON'), ('Ang', 'PERSON')]
909814848946671616;2017-09-18 16:22:18;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;People in Orlando still has no power.;[('Orlando', 'LOCATION')]
909814851001872384;2017-09-18 16:22:18;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;Forgot I promised Milah we'd make apple pie cookies.;[('Milah', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814852805328896;2017-09-18 16:22:19;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;Thank God for Samsung Pay;[('Thank', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('God', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Samsung', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814851752644608;2017-09-18 16:22:18;Hoboken, NJ;40.73871176;-74.02930508;Lunch to celebrate the office move (@ Ubu in Hoboken, NJ) https://t.co/rrChc9MmYj https://t.co/d8pXPwI9O1;[('Hoboken', 'LOCATION'), ('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909814855120568320;2017-09-18 16:22:19;Manhattan, NY;40.72221048;-73.98673912;Night 2 Of A Murder Of Crows III BackStage_ . . #amoc #moc #music #live #show #mercurylounge… https://t.co/vLJHSkXcmu;[('Crows', 'MISC'), ('III', 'MISC')]
909814863077273605;2017-09-18 16:22:21;Hasbrouck Heights, NJ;40.861731500000005;-74.07425199999999;But both sides are to blame for Charlottesville. All started when some moron decided to take down a statue https://t.co/0bBQDSMpql;[('Charlottesville', 'LOCATION')]
909814863966355456;2017-09-18 16:22:21;Secaucus, NJ;40.7895453;-74.0565298;Join the DFS team! See our latest #job opening here: https://t.co/0WDDD5fXCy #FacilitiesMgmt #Secaucus, NJ #Hiring #CareerArc;[('DFS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909814866784935938;2017-09-18 16:22:22;Elizabeth, NJ;40.6639916;-74.2107006;Want to work in #Elizabeth, NJ? View our latest opening: https://t.co/Z8fotzkHBC #Transportation #Job #Jobs #Hiring #CareerArc;[('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909814868743802881;2017-09-18 16:22:22;Manhattan, NY;40.80616;-73.94701;Visit Us Today. Harlem Haberdashery 245 Lenox Ave. Bet. 122nd & 123rd St. Harlem, NYC . Shop… https://t.co/hq3WnAsd09;[('Harlem', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Haberdashery', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lenox', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ave', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bet', 'LOCATION'), ('Harlem', 'LOCATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814891762077696;2017-09-18 16:22:28;New York, NY;40.705597499999996;-73.977717;Global Citizen Festival, Central Park NYC | LIVE on @YouTube presented by @TMobile https://t.co/1QK1fH2Fsu;[('Global', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Citizen', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Festival', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Central', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814897050923008;2017-09-18 16:22:29;Levittown, NY;40.7259336;-73.5142921;This #job might be a great fit for you: Pharmacy Technician - https://t.co/ENIPOnH9zC #Healthcare #Levittown, NY #Hiring #CareerArc;[('Pharmacy', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Technician', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909814918500769794;2017-09-18 16:22:34;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;I love upcoming Legends. I decided to Stan forever. https://t.co/weRMcNMQ5V;[('Stan', 'PERSON')]
909814919918440448;2017-09-18 16:22:35;North Brunswick, NJ;40.4457045;-74.473067;Kevin Hart was beating that shit up 😂😂😂;[('Kevin', 'PERSON'), ('Hart', 'PERSON')]
909814921847885825;2017-09-18 16:22:35;Connecticut, USA;41.500753;-72.757385;@ReflectionsofJM @TheRealJonAdams @FLOTUS AW,,,sweet;[('AW', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814928042840065;2017-09-18 16:22:37;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Ugh I think I like Cardi B now;[('Cardi', 'PERSON')]
909814937509289984;2017-09-18 16:22:39;Manhattan, NY;40.7299;-73.9914;Astor Place, NYC - With a jacket like that you have to request a portrait- Fashion Week -… https://t.co/CagdmNeKbC;[('Astor', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Place', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814940529131520;2017-09-18 16:22:40;Manhattan, NY;40.7609682;-73.9780638;This #job might be a great fit for you: Associate Manager, Audience Management & Activation - https://t.co/OUGJIm6oAK #Marketing NY;[('Audience', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Management', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Activation', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814944882884608;2017-09-18 16:22:41;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;The Literary Cat https://t.co/GctOzvIt3R;[('Literary', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Cat', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814949802856449;2017-09-18 16:22:42;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;@chloevevrier here's a birthday joke for you: Why did Tommy hit his birthday cake with a hammer? It was a Poundcake!;[('Tommy', 'PERSON')]
909814961442099205;2017-09-18 16:22:45;New York, USA;43.092671;-75.787841;Cleared: Incident on #I90NYSThruway EB from After Exit 34 (I-90) - Canastota (Rte 13) to Exit 34 (I-90) - Canastota (Rte 13);[('Canastota', 'LOCATION'), ('Canastota', 'LOCATION')]
909814962167656450;2017-09-18 16:22:45;New York, USA;43.092671;-75.787841;Cleared: Incident on #I90NYSThruway EB from After Exit 34 (I-90) - Canastota (Rte 13) to Exit 34 (I-90) - Canastota (Rte 13);[('Canastota', 'LOCATION'), ('Canastota', 'LOCATION')]
909814962037694465;2017-09-18 16:22:45;Manhattan, NY;40.70288699;-74.01726365;I'm at Statue of Liberty Ferry in New York, NY https://t.co/Hqs04fRCvA;[('Statue', 'LOCATION'), ('of', 'LOCATION'), ('Liberty', 'LOCATION'), ('Ferry', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909814963065229313;2017-09-18 16:22:45;Greenburgh, NY;41.05674;-73.83548;Cleared: Construction on #I287CrossWestchesterExpwy EB from 0.0 to Before Exit 6 (I-287) - Broadway (Rte 22);[('Before', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Exit', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814966974390272;2017-09-18 16:22:46;Ridgefield, NJ;40.830002;-74.011779;"""Whatchu mean you don't give head?"" https://t.co/2TTGNwWvPs";[('Whatchu', 'PERSON')]
909814979066396673;2017-09-18 16:22:49;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;#hijo definicion.. LEELO @ New York, New York https://t.co/ewi0sN9FOY;[('LEELO', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909814979041280001;2017-09-18 16:22:49;Manhattan, NY;40.78128;-73.96037;Behind the scenes on a Monday morning at the Neue Galerie. #zezeflowers @ Neue Galerie New York https://t.co/J6ykXdIo7J;[('Neue', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Galerie', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Neue', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Galerie', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('New', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('York', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814985991364608;2017-09-18 16:22:50;Manhattan, NY;40.745278;-74.002222;Is there life on Mars? 🔴 @ Chelsea, Manhattan https://t.co/g5lOjggvgS;[('Chelsea', 'PERSON'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909814991632588800;2017-09-18 16:22:52;Manhattan, NY;40.7609682;-73.9780638;We're #hiring! Click to apply: Quantitative Analyst III - Qualitative Validation - https://t.co/HkbsAFOqbA #BusinessMgmt NY #Job #Jobs;[('Quantitative', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Analyst', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('III', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Qualitative', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Validation', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814993779953665;2017-09-18 16:22:52;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@KayBurley @SkyNews Is this all to do with what I heard. Rupert Murdoch wants Boris Johnson as PM because he said h… https://t.co/hLsQpP9tQy;[('Rupert', 'PERSON'), ('Murdoch', 'PERSON'), ('Boris', 'PERSON'), ('Johnson', 'PERSON')]
909814996066082820;2017-09-18 16:22:53;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;There's no place for hateful people at Dollywood, Mary Kate, so maybe this is for the best. https://t.co/LxRtNYueAf;[('Dollywood', 'LOCATION'), ('Mary', 'PERSON'), ('Kate', 'PERSON')]
909814997445955584;2017-09-18 16:22:53;Manhattan, NY;40.80616;-73.94701;Visit Us Today. Harlem Haberdashery 245 Lenox Ave. Bet. 122nd & 123rd St. Harlem, NYC . Shop… https://t.co/e9FUSmLM61;[('Harlem', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Haberdashery', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lenox', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ave', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bet', 'LOCATION'), ('Harlem', 'LOCATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909814999073398789;2017-09-18 16:22:53;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;educational  criminalization  systems   do not have  the right  to play  with  secirity  of USA and American people livelihoods  with;[('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('American', 'MISC')]
909815002659516416;2017-09-18 16:22:54;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;& Strawberry Swing - Frank Ocean will be played at my funeral while everyone wears white 🙃;[('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Strawberry', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Swing', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Frank', 'PERSON'), ('Ocean', 'PERSON')]
909815013459632128;2017-09-18 16:22:57;Barclays Center;40.68312;-73.975979;Kyrie Irving is likely a calculated sociopath, such as myself.. or he could just be a good guy with a peach fuzz be… https://t.co/5RhTiPd4wb;[('Kyrie', 'PERSON'), ('Irving', 'PERSON')]
909815017696096256;2017-09-18 16:22:58;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Spicer should be a footnote not a novelty act. He lied repeatedly and abetted a criminal, white supremacist agenda.;[('Spicer', 'PERSON')]
909815020237750272;2017-09-18 16:22:59;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;Lmaoo ya dun kno! https://t.co/xe7RQi7Aca;[('Lmaoo', 'PERSON')]
909815022649581568;2017-09-18 16:22:59;Massachusetts, USA;42.036939000000004;-71.683502;Boof blunt to the face to start my day;[('Boof', 'PERSON')]
909815028022362112;2017-09-18 16:23:00;Connecticut, USA;41.6717648;-72.9492703;This #job might be a great fit for you: Pharmacy Technician - https://t.co/cBvBilBsfW #Healthcare #Bristol, CT #Hiring #CareerArc;[('Pharmacy', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Technician', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815043344257024;2017-09-18 16:23:04;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;@FifthHarmony This is their BEST ALBUM and their voices mesh well together... without Camila 🤷🏽‍♂️;[('Camila', 'PERSON')]
909815055012827137;2017-09-18 16:23:07;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;Bro just retire https://t.co/xXNvA5norq;[('Bro', 'LOCATION')]
909815068229079041;2017-09-18 16:23:10;Queens, NY;40.68189;-73.76555;TONIGHT!!!! I'm inside Club Dubai aka Club Lornas Aka Queen OfThe Sea!!!! We taking it back… https://t.co/ND6uYo3SYJ;[('Club', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Dubai', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('aka', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lornas', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Aka', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Queen', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('OfThe', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sea', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815095680569345;2017-09-18 16:23:17;Queens, NY;40.77725;-73.87261111;☺️ for my flight ❤️ @ La Guardia Airport https://t.co/NaDIwgDsLD;[('La', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Guardia', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Airport', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815098851696641;2017-09-18 16:23:17;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Daddy Asf. 😋⭐️😍🦋 https://t.co/VwvHknl5o0;[('Daddy', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Asf', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815114190204928;2017-09-18 16:23:21;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;NYC Parks Wildlife Unit paid us a visit at the market yesterday!  There are coyotes in Riverdale!?! #Coyotes… https://t.co/rS3bNpd5cR;[('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Parks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Wildlife', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Unit', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Riverdale', 'LOCATION')]
909815120594948096;2017-09-18 16:23:22;Merrick, NY;40.652444;-73.55287100000001;Join us in Huntington for the Rally to KILL THE GRAHAM CASSIDY ACA BILL!!   Wed.3:30-5pm. Huntington, NY.  NW corne… https://t.co/jer1cxAJjz;[('Huntington', 'LOCATION'), ('GRAHAM', 'PERSON'), ('ACA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Huntington', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815133299453952;2017-09-18 16:23:25;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;A woman was sexually assaulted in an off-campus house at UMD after a suspect broke into the home through a window. https://t.co/moENvlu6e2;[('UMD', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815143541936128;2017-09-18 16:23:28;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;Southern Regional Surf Club practice is cancelled today. Please go home after school. @HCPolice @LongBeachTwpPD;[('Southern', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Regional', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Surf', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815151083311104;2017-09-18 16:23:30;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;I am pumped for Laver Cup. Federer-Nadal together as a doubles pairing would be awesome.;[('Laver', 'MISC'), ('Cup', 'MISC'), ('Federer-Nadal', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815155520823296;2017-09-18 16:23:31;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Never cried when Pac died, but I probably will when Latty David does.;[('Pac', 'PERSON'), ('Latty', 'PERSON'), ('David', 'PERSON')]
909815162953183232;2017-09-18 16:23:33;Manhattan, NY;40.77274259;-73.972216;Just posted a photo @ Central Park https://t.co/hkj7CTgc83;[('Central', 'LOCATION'), ('Park', 'LOCATION')]
909815166212214787;2017-09-18 16:23:33;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Elite NYC Escorts DATING, #International Escorts, Manhattan, #NYCESCORTS #ELITE #SEXY #VIP 646-575-4117… https://t.co/eII1zdI6UZ;[('Elite', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DATING', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909815173241860097;2017-09-18 16:23:35;Manhattan, NY;40.74647751;-73.98383941;"#KendrickLamar type beat ""No Bass"" prod. By @Firstletter1 via #YouTube https://t.co/HaUFAvbA53 #Like #Subscribe #Purchasetracks";[('Bass', 'MISC')]
909815179164053505;2017-09-18 16:23:36;Greenburgh, NY;41.05787;-73.83666;Accident, center lane blocked in #Tarrytown on The NY State Thruway SB at Thruway, stop and go traffic back to X10, delay of 19 mins;[('NY', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('State', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Thruway', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SB', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Thruway', 'LOCATION')]
909815202446663680;2017-09-18 16:23:42;Manhattan, NY;40.7127837;-74.0059413;Want to work at Flik, Premier Hospitality? We're #hiring in #NewYork, NY! Click for details: https://t.co/HR49ud2V3H #Hospitality #Job;[('Flik', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815202878603265;2017-09-18 16:23:42;Manhattan, NY;40.7070045;-74.0035553;A design story to start the week: @StandardWax Home Fragrances are made in Phoenix, Arizona and… https://t.co/GYGyouFbFe;[('Phoenix', 'LOCATION'), ('Arizona', 'LOCATION')]
909815214434025472;2017-09-18 16:23:45;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;What a beer to bring in 50th. @HillFarmstead Karma Emulsion @blindtigernyc 😍🍻🎂;[('Karma', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Emulsion', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815217667833857;2017-09-18 16:23:46;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;I think 315ers have the best camper etiquette.  Tell you what a Wollcott resident did while staying in s friend's camper. @Radio_951 #roc;[('Wollcott', 'LOCATION')]
909815222571069440;2017-09-18 16:23:47;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;@JayOsyrus Yup, Emmy for lead actor in a limited series, you know my son had to finesse 💪🏼;[('Emmy', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815231139975168;2017-09-18 16:23:49;Tappan Zee High School;41.049003;-73.953941;Please donate money to help with hurrican relief at a school in need in Port Arthur, TX! You can donate in the libr… https://t.co/PqxuiPWtGh;[('Port', 'LOCATION'), ('Arthur', 'LOCATION'), ('TX', 'LOCATION')]
909815237351788544;2017-09-18 16:23:50;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;Looking for a couple stand in's for a rehearsal tomorrow 8am-10:30am $30, NYC. Must be able to read cue cards! Laurenwaterscasting@gmail.com;[('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815236563279872;2017-09-18 16:23:50;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Elite NYC Escorts DATING, #International Escorts, Manhattan, #NYCESCORTS #ELITE #SEXY #VIP 646-575-4117… https://t.co/CDKQsC8hnI;[('Elite', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DATING', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909815243555164160;2017-09-18 16:23:52;Queens, NY;40.74757;-73.85614;Another Anthony Kiedis shot from last night. Still shocked I got to do this one. Nostalgic vibes… https://t.co/gsakYaT7kd;[('Anthony', 'PERSON'), ('Kiedis', 'PERSON')]
909815254196113408;2017-09-18 16:23:54;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Wrestling Podcast Super Bowl (according to my polls earlier).  Who's your favorite?;[('Wrestling', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Podcast', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Super', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bowl', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815263612125184;2017-09-18 16:23:57;Kearny, NJ;40.7684342;-74.1454214;Can you recommend anyone for this #job? Physician, $25K Sign On Bonus! - https://t.co/2tGpBMK4Zl #Physician #Kearny, NJ #Veterans #Hiring;[('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909815268347711493;2017-09-18 16:23:58;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;I gave in. I'll be in the Midwest for thanksgiving;[('Midwest', 'LOCATION')]
909815268381257729;2017-09-18 16:23:58;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;#Ways  #Gibraltar   The signing of the GI Bill. Franklin Delano Roosevelt. https://t.co/U1fJJiuH89;[('GI', 'MISC'), ('Bill', 'MISC'), ('Franklin', 'PERSON'), ('Delano', 'PERSON'), ('Roosevelt', 'PERSON')]
909815274022494208;2017-09-18 16:23:59;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@fackinpeter @JedediahBila I suggested the Julie and Jed show be picked up by a station. That would be Must See Tv.;[('Julie', 'PERSON'), ('Jed', 'PERSON')]
909815279198359556;2017-09-18 16:24:00;New Jersey, USA;39.905048;-75.128254;Cleared: Incident on #I76 WB at Walt Whitman Bridge;[('WB', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Walt', 'LOCATION'), ('Whitman', 'LOCATION'), ('Bridge', 'LOCATION')]
909815279202553857;2017-09-18 16:24:00;New Jersey, USA;39.905048;-75.128254;Cleared: Incident on #I76 WB at Walt Whitman Bridge;[('WB', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Walt', 'LOCATION'), ('Whitman', 'LOCATION'), ('Bridge', 'LOCATION')]
909815279684804608;2017-09-18 16:24:00;Queens, NY;40.7595044;-73.9271644;If you're looking for work in #NewYork, NY, check out this #job: https://t.co/428t7J3yXC #CitiCareers #ProductMgmt #Hiring #CareerArc;[('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815289675730944;2017-09-18 16:24:03;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Elite NYC Escorts DATING, #International Escorts, Manhattan, #NYCESCORTS #ELITE #SEXY #VIP 646-575-4117… https://t.co/dNCwC6gouy;[('Elite', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DATING', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909815294318784512;2017-09-18 16:24:04;Bloomfield, NJ;40.8085105;-74.1873045;LMFAOOOOO this be you @___jmxo https://t.co/y1wEyWOZnM;[('LMFAOOO', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815307363082240;2017-09-18 16:24:07;Yonkers, NY;40.944567500000005;-73.86085700000001;@xboxuk @bateson87 @EAAccess If I get Ea Access now do I still get it ?;[('Ea', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Access', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815307413409794;2017-09-18 16:24:07;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;They also need to establish the city of Metropolis. Need to get the know the people there, not just see it all get destroyed for 10 minutes.;[('Metropolis', 'LOCATION')]
909815305987411969;2017-09-18 16:24:07;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Maria from @MaketheRoadNY holds photos of friends whose parents are tps recipients https://t.co/foQ1xEqIzH;[('Maria', 'PERSON')]
909815318557503488;2017-09-18 16:24:10;Florham Park, NJ;40.787878;-74.3882072;Can you recommend anyone for this #job in #FlorhamPark, NJ? https://t.co/6cLGHdsqYQ #Finance #Hiring #CareerArc;[('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909815319853768705;2017-09-18 16:24:10;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;@erugli Yes, it was most certainly French :);[('French', 'MISC')]
909815321216847872;2017-09-18 16:24:10;Edison, NJ;40.5387865;-74.377998;Some of us are ugly, Lauren. https://t.co/srTpVaqXpU;[('Lauren', 'PERSON')]
909815332201750536;2017-09-18 16:24:13;Florham Park, NJ;40.774339;-74.399048;🚨Game time alert🚨  #IUvsPSU will kickoff at 3:30 p.m. in Beaver Stadium and air on @BigTenNetwork.  #WeAre https://t.co/EYv248jcfu;[('Beaver', 'LOCATION'), ('Stadium', 'LOCATION')]
909815340871438342;2017-09-18 16:24:15;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;I just realized Fuller House AND Transparent premiere on Friday. https://t.co/2lUJ8hR0wB;[('Fuller', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('House', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815344663064576;2017-09-18 16:24:16;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;#FMMarsudi met with FM of #Namibia, H.E Netumbo Nandi-Ndaitwah at the sidelines of #UNGA #SMUPBB72  -- Strengthenin… https://t.co/ZeTYf8u1LX;[('Netumbo', 'PERSON'), ('Nandi-Ndaitwah', 'PERSON'), ('Strengthenin', 'PERSON')]
909815354477694976;2017-09-18 16:24:18;Queens, NY;40.64610466;-73.78438205;#crazy #boomerang @ John F. Kennedy International Airport https://t.co/Y9ZSbkW4b2;[('John', 'PERSON'), ('F', 'PERSON'), ('Kennedy', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('International', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Airport', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815356360990720;2017-09-18 16:24:19;Croton-on-Hudson, NY;41.251326;-73.8972405;Mafia Barbie is projecting again. https://t.co/nzRAXS3jjO;[('Barbie', 'PERSON')]
909815369484861441;2017-09-18 16:24:22;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Elite NYC Escorts DATING, #International Escorts, Manhattan, #NYCESCORTS #ELITE #SEXY #VIP 646-575-4117… https://t.co/GGLVsQRqRx;[('Elite', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DATING', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909815370067927040;2017-09-18 16:24:22;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;Give it to @TonyAvella. 3 dead & 16 injured this morning due to speed in his district on Northern Blvd. & he's here… https://t.co/w3FJjP3c3Q;[('Northern', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Blvd', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815379609968642;2017-09-18 16:24:24;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;"@Gidmeister @dcalrider @chrgdup1973 HEY GULLIBLE FOOL   SPEND THE $1.99 & FIND OUT  ""Secret History of the Democrat… https://t.co/Bf5EcuY7SM";[('Democrat', 'MISC')]
909815384450240513;2017-09-18 16:24:25;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;appollingy filthy disgrace  Your Dems  abominable egregiously heinousness crimes of treason  action  call into question destructive veil;[('Your', 'MISC'), ('Dems', 'MISC')]
909815396277956608;2017-09-18 16:24:28;Teaneck, NJ;40.8975992;-74.0159727;Interested in a #job in #Teaneck, NJ? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/a2hj8uWpN7 #IT #Hiring;[('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909815398325014539;2017-09-18 16:24:29;Port Washington, NY;40.829604;-73.6823705;@2ez_nassie, FB need to DM. Thank you.;[('FB', 'LOCATION'), ('DM', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815400669511680;2017-09-18 16:24:29;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Oh snap! Chance The Rapper and Young Thug were spotted in the studio together: https://t.co/T4xKq89MKY https://t.co/seTeofulX9;[('Rapper', 'MISC'), ('Young', 'PERSON'), ('Thug', 'PERSON')]
909815408588316672;2017-09-18 16:24:31;Denville, NJ;40.8923212;-74.4773775;Join the BAYADA team! See our latest #job opening here: https://t.co/Gd0mYpZFje #Healthcare #Denville, NJ #Hiring #CareerArc;[('BAYADA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909815423973064709;2017-09-18 16:24:35;New York, NY;40.705597499999996;-73.977717;It's been 4 years since 1,000 NYers marched on Wall Street to #endAIDS w/a #RobinHoodTax https://t.co/QC8w8FcY4J https://t.co/Rxx7QQifhO;[('NYers', 'PERSON'), ('Wall', 'LOCATION'), ('Street', 'LOCATION')]
909815428284915712;2017-09-18 16:24:36;Brooklyn, NY;40.6714578;-73.9580179;Man Fatally Shot Outside Crown Heights Deli, Police Say (790 FRANKLIN AVE) #NYC #NewYorkCity https://t.co/Ir1W70Gm8B;[('Heights', 'PERSON'), ('Deli', 'PERSON')]
909815428653961217;2017-09-18 16:24:36;Farmingdale, NY;40.7320385;-73.44818000000001;@BMcClelland24 teaching us to App Smash using Aww & ScreenCastify!@PrincipalPena https://t.co/hB736I558y;[('App', 'MISC'), ('Smash', 'MISC')]
909815435456954368;2017-09-18 16:24:38;Brooklyn, NY;40.6781784;-73.9441579;Can you recommend anyone for this #job? Dyson Sales Expert, Part Time - Brooklyn, NY - https://t.co/6xNbpNco4F #Retail #NewYork, NY;[('Dyson', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sales', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Expert', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Part', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Time', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Brooklyn', 'LOCATION')]
909815443350855682;2017-09-18 16:24:39;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@katyhersh @peterajoseph Happy 1 year adopted, Gary!!;[('Gary', 'PERSON')]
909815444860801025;2017-09-18 16:24:40;Duane Reade;40.738681;-73.999368;@ACMenes Welp enjoy your applesauce;[('Welp', 'PERSON')]
909815447750668289;2017-09-18 16:24:40;White Plains, NY;41.0262045;-73.754737;"""We're pissed."" Excellent hashtag for UT fans today. #Pissed";[('UT', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815449478672384;2017-09-18 16:24:41;Manhattan, NY;40.71306941;-74.01313305;I'm at One World Trade Center - @onewtc in New York, NY https://t.co/3rTAvTabKI;[('World', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trade', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Center', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815450040782849;2017-09-18 16:24:41;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Life's too short to not bop to Dua Lipa's album;[('Dua', 'LOCATION')]
909815453333229569;2017-09-18 16:24:42;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@MCoveteur a nice jerk wing or a shot of Jack D;[('Jack', 'PERSON')]
909815455224930304;2017-09-18 16:24:42;West Freehold, NJ;40.216589;-74.288077;Action shots of Zeke vs Denver D last night #Cowboys #CowboysNation #Broncos #SNF https://t.co/ohYqm9GJu5;[('Zeke', 'LOCATION'), ('Denver', 'LOCATION')]
909815463479332864;2017-09-18 16:24:44;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;@TPM Sir Patrick could do it better! https://t.co/AaLRiAi627;[('Patrick', 'PERSON')]
909815472996065280;2017-09-18 16:24:46;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@mog7546 I saw that Mike but it just depressed me. There doesn't seem to be a way out, around or through.;[('Mike', 'PERSON')]
909815474921332737;2017-09-18 16:24:47;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;uuegularaties of towards law and order  I call to American people  urgency  to demand  for putting stop  to numerous you Dems party  f;[('American', 'MISC'), ('Dems', 'MISC')]
909815483746148352;2017-09-18 16:24:49;Plainview, NY;40.783516500000005;-73.47405;@SpectreFGC I don't want to be surrounded with Lylat negative individuals 😭😭;[('Lylat', 'PERSON')]
909815491761459200;2017-09-18 16:24:51;Pace University Law School;41.03984;-73.765812;Pace Pres. Marvin Krislov w/student Lisdy Contreras Giron & Congresswoman Nita Lowey at Pace DACA DREAM Act Roundta… https://t.co/baLIruiOEn;[('Marvin', 'PERSON'), ('Krislov', 'PERSON'), ('Lisdy', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Contreras', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Giron', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Congresswoman', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nita', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lowey', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pace', 'LOCATION'), ('DACA', 'LOCATION'), ('Roundta', 'PERSON')]
909815513588621312;2017-09-18 16:24:56;Port Washington, NY;40.829604;-73.6823705;@2ez_nassie, FB need to DM. Thank you.;[('FB', 'LOCATION'), ('DM', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815522908352516;2017-09-18 16:24:58;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;Elite NYC Escorts DATING, #International Escorts, Manhattan, #NYCESCORTS #ELITE #SEXY #VIP 646-575-4117… https://t.co/l7VSK94afQ;[('Elite', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DATING', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909815525278195712;2017-09-18 16:24:59;Piscataway, NJ;40.551769500000006;-74.466483;Kill says Gio Rescigno is a pretty good player who has hung in there. He and Zach Allen are assistant coaches, so to speak. #rutgers;[('Gio', 'PERSON'), ('Rescigno', 'PERSON'), ('Zach', 'PERSON'), ('Allen', 'PERSON')]
909815527840927744;2017-09-18 16:25:00;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;~ The dream is free, the hustles sold separately #MondayMotivation 🌸✌🏼✨📸 @aegphoto ~ @ New York,… https://t.co/adDdTQzGrI;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909815528730120195;2017-09-18 16:25:00;Manhattan, NY;40.72221048;-73.98673912;A MURDER OF CROWS III Night 2 Hangin With Shawn, killer set! #amoc #moc #neonkross #music #live… https://t.co/F05HnxaVnl;[('Hangin', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('With', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Shawn', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815530680397824;2017-09-18 16:25:00;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;"@theswordcom Why do I, a former #gayporn actor, have ""Little Respect (If Any) 4 Porn Actors, Especially Black Ones"" https://t.co/NMmD8VtuVn";[('Little', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Respect', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Porn', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Actors', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Especially', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Black', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ones', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815525865394179;2017-09-18 16:24:59;Connecticut, USA;41.500753;-72.757385;Can't wait. I love Tomb Raider and I really love #AliciaVikander 😍 https://t.co/HOVBUTeLMT;[('Tomb', 'PERSON'), ('Raider', 'PERSON')]
909815540738347010;2017-09-18 16:25:03;Manhattan, NY;40.806702;-73.967413;Nice place to sit outside. (@ Louis Kossuth Memorial in New York, NY) https://t.co/SPqMVc9vjG;[('Nice', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Louis', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Kossuth', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Memorial', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815543850520576;2017-09-18 16:25:03;Manhattan, NY;40.71174252;-74.01293885;I'm at National September 11 Memorial & Museum in New York, NY https://t.co/PupgxozuFk;[('&', 'LOCATION'), ('Museum', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815555208572929;2017-09-18 16:25:06;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;🌓 @ New York, New York https://t.co/PFcH2Rl6tk;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909815577325252610;2017-09-18 16:25:11;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@rking_19 Same brain freezes that allow staff to write (and then not read) was  done in 1988 w Catastrophic Cov Act… https://t.co/R2jyZosir4;[('Catastrophic', 'PERSON')]
909815577258090496;2017-09-18 16:25:11;Brooklyn, NY;40.6781784;-73.9441579;We're #hiring! Click to apply: Dyson Sales Expert, Part Time - Brooklyn & Long Island, NY - https://t.co/7BMjLWThx4 #Sales #Brooklyn, NY;[('Dyson', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sales', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Expert', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Part', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Time', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Brooklyn', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Long', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Island', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815603317194752;2017-09-18 16:25:18;Manhattan, NY;40.7602619;-73.9932872;We're #hiring! Click to apply: Administrative Assistant/ Analyst - https://t.co/jZxdsfrRUn #Finance #NewYork, NY #Job #Jobs #CareerArc;[('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815604340604928;2017-09-18 16:25:18;Manhattan, NY;40.76912;-73.9815581;Can you recommend anyone for this #job? Director of Operations - https://t.co/aAIgtpmUDT #BusinessMgmt #NewYork, NY #Hiring;[('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815621080293376;2017-09-18 16:25:22;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;ART x GLAM Beauty, inc. is now accepting Halloween Bookings! Book us now to secure your… https://t.co/mJ9ZcIblSE;[('ART', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('GLAM', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Beauty', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Halloween', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bookings', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815622833524737;2017-09-18 16:25:22;New York, USA;44.49691952;-73.49698919;I'm at Pleasant Corner Restaurant in Keeseville, NY https://t.co/HhoFZmRH91;[('Pleasant', 'LOCATION'), ('Corner', 'LOCATION'), ('Restaurant', 'LOCATION'), ('Keeseville', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815626386026498;2017-09-18 16:25:23;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;ISIS ‘Hit Squads’ Are Using The Refugee Program To Infiltrate Western Nations  https://t.co/UgwlXjXt3j;[('ISIS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Refugee', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Program', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('To', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Infiltrate', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Western', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nations', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815636502745088;2017-09-18 16:25:25;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;"I felt like a little kid today, got home An couldn't wait to tell parents ""I Went Pee Pee in the potty"" #RenalFailureProblems";[('Pee', 'PERSON'), ('Pee', 'PERSON')]
909815644085944320;2017-09-18 16:25:27;Residence of the Norwegian Consul General;40.754743;-73.968158;"Venezuelan violinist and activist @WuillyArteaga says ""even though we've lost more than 120 people, the music is st… https://t.co/QwuvgS5b42";[('Venezuelan', 'MISC')]
909815649584779265;2017-09-18 16:25:29;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;So great seeing Yannick on New York City's streets! We're here to prioritise issues of African youth and women at U… https://t.co/zfYMCMm81I;[('Yannick', 'PERSON'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('African', 'MISC')]
909815663799173121;2017-09-18 16:25:32;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;@GSKFANZ Hiiii hello 🙋🏽🙋🏽🙋🏽🙋🏽 *points at self*;[('Hiii', 'PERSON')]
909815675417448449;2017-09-18 16:25:35;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Louis Vuitton Opens at The Shops at Clearfork, TX – https://t.co/WCi39AZznO https://t.co/kumYiOcHf4;[('Louis', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Vuitton', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Opens', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('The', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Shops', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Clearfork', 'LOCATION'), ('TX', 'LOCATION')]
909815679125213186;2017-09-18 16:25:36;Connecticut, USA;41.500753;-72.757385;Elite NYC Escorts DATING, #International Escorts, Manhattan, #NYCESCORTS #ELITE #SEXY #VIP 646-575-4117… https://t.co/xR1VsLuaWH;[('Elite', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DATING', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909815704580435968;2017-09-18 16:25:42;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;Africa with it nice;[('Africa', 'LOCATION')]
909815705599713280;2017-09-18 16:25:42;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;allinig into incredible monsrose  cult of Communism leftist ideology  compounding to scaring  situation  of numerous challengers;[('Communism', 'MISC')]
909815708304818177;2017-09-18 16:25:43;New York, USA;43.1138828;-75.5954196;We're #hiring! Click to apply: Floor Sales Associate - https://t.co/EZ28AW7MXl #Hospitality #Verona, NY #Job #Jobs #CareerArc;[('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815743587418112;2017-09-18 16:25:51;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;LMAO oh twitter how I love u https://t.co/gCr6vmn4dn;[('LMAO', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815744774500353;2017-09-18 16:25:51;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;So Fri had a cliffhanger with #jarlena & Bon-Bon & today NADA 🤔🤔🤔 ok LoL #days;[('Fri', 'MISC'), ('#jarlena', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bon-Bon', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NADA', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815757114048512;2017-09-18 16:25:54;Stamford, CT;41.0983345;-73.554097;Viewed a different way... KU -41 Bay -30 @ ISU -20 @ WVU -15.5 @ TT -14.5 KSU -13 TCU -11.5 @ UT -9 OU even  Anythi… https://t.co/6KJah7AqaP;[('ISU', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('WVU', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('KSU', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('TCU', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UT', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('OU', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Anythi', 'PERSON')]
909815761241243648;2017-09-18 16:25:55;New York, USA;42.4745857;-78.695668;Just posted a photo @ Allegany State Park https://t.co/9Mv4WDmw6U;[('Allegany', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('State', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Park', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815765087465472;2017-09-18 16:25:56;East Orange, NJ;40.766601;-74.214139;@sik0simmons you sure that's Cari?;[('Cari', 'PERSON')]
909815766362361856;2017-09-18 16:25:56;Newark, NJ;40.6925;-74.1686;Airport shenanigans before take off. Later Jersey! It's been real. #Jersey #ocean #asburypark… https://t.co/EsJ2JgTqFA;[('Later', 'LOCATION'), ('Jersey', 'LOCATION')]
909815769252470784;2017-09-18 16:25:57;United Nations;40.749224;-73.968673;SDGs Media Zone will soon feature #EquatorPrize2017 winners  Follow @UNDPLive #GlobalGoalsWeek #UNGA https://t.co/GdnCoIpOoM;[('SDGs', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Media', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Zone', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815771165024256;2017-09-18 16:25:58;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;Know anyone looking to start a career in Real Estate? #realestate #KellerWilliamsRealty #Residential #Commercial… https://t.co/KKIbczDFME;[('Real', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Estate', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815774335954945;2017-09-18 16:25:58;Manhattan, NY;40.7531899;-73.98897;I swear it was Friday 5 minutes ago @ Manhattan in New York https://t.co/QdyFKeuPWf;[('Manhattan', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909815777183670272;2017-09-18 16:25:59;West Freehold, NJ;40.2136754;-74.3000878;Interested in a #job in #FreeholdTownship, NJ? This could be a great fit: https://t.co/GBe6iYG3g0 #Retail #Hiring #CareerArc;[('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909815782443503616;2017-09-18 16:26:00;Manhattan, NY;40.71948;-74.00063;Look familiar? This is the back of our shop in SoHo when it was occupied by it's previous… https://t.co/245UUhVzc0;[('SoHo', 'LOCATION')]
909815784892854272;2017-09-18 16:26:01;White Plains, NY;41.0247477;-73.7631028;#AvailableNow | SF AF1 Mid 'Mars Stone' by @nikesportswear. $160 USD. Doors are open until 8PM.… https://t.co/BXBmrvlXAC;[('Mars', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Stone', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815785702477824;2017-09-18 16:26:01;Massachusetts, USA;42.036939000000004;-71.683502;Finally made it back 2 Boston 2 celebrate BB19 finale w/ my familia! #BB19 #bigbrother #BigBrother19 #bbad #BostonStrong #bbkevin #Familia;[('Boston', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815786541342720;2017-09-18 16:26:01;Hicksville, NY;40.7681405;-73.5300925;Trump supporters are as diverse as the day is long Amen! #MAGA https://t.co/NqP3Gewtsg;[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Amen', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815792396619782;2017-09-18 16:26:03;North Haledon, NJ;40.9623625;-74.1899585;Dr. Lee is actually the greatest lmao;[('Lee', 'PERSON')]
909815793319399424;2017-09-18 16:26:03;Elizabeth, NJ;40.662479;-74.19652450000001;This is simply buggin because his wife is currently pregnant. My God. https://t.co/pSuxqxT37l;[('God', 'PERSON')]
909815804404862976;2017-09-18 16:26:05;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;At UN High Level Meeting on Hurricane Irma response, @CUBAONU Min. highlights active Cuba support to other affected Caribbean nations.;[('UN', 'LOCATION'), ('Irma', 'PERSON'), ('Cuba', 'LOCATION'), ('Caribbean', 'LOCATION')]
909815813686906887;2017-09-18 16:26:08;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;I'd like to go to SIGACCESS Conference on Computers and Accessibility https://t.co/qbhT60jsgO;[('SIGACCESS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Conference', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('on', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Computers', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815826760503296;2017-09-18 16:26:11;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;@snowbubbleon @lindsayarnold @Jordan_Fisher Lindsay? You have my entire family voting for you! Knock them dead!  :);[('Lindsay', 'PERSON')]
909815830640173056;2017-09-18 16:26:12;New Brunswick, NJ;40.4862157;-74.4518188;If you're looking for work in #NewBrunswick, NJ, check out this #job: https://t.co/oddmYWiEQP #Hiring #CareerArc;[('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909815847597826049;2017-09-18 16:26:16;Manhattan, NY;40.72604;-74.00122;bikevibe NYC is out now! Head to bikevibe.no to get your copy, packed full of cycling stories… https://t.co/R9H2GK3gU2;[('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815849220849664;2017-09-18 16:26:16;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;Forgot Kindle Passcode? Follow these Instructions! https://t.co/oyb6ymjRDy #kindlefire #amazonkindle #kindlesupport https://t.co/LOa43KsEv2;[('Forgot', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Kindle', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Passcode', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815860168183808;2017-09-18 16:26:19;Bayonne, NJ;40.6707835;-74.10636600000001;Lmaoo QTNA!!!!!!! Cause i  am SHOOKETH !!!! Ayo @___billyhunda33 u running KD fake account?? https://t.co/yO8KfX8ZyX;[('Lmaoo', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('QTNA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SHOOKETH', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ayo', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815863766863873;2017-09-18 16:26:20;Jersey City, NJ;40.7180015;-74.066663;@keithellison @kartpath I will be overjoyed when you get become US Rep AND Chair of the DNC. Can’t wait to see what… https://t.co/YfcrC31EAD;[('US', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Rep', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('AND', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chair', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DNC', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815865436143621;2017-09-18 16:26:20;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Whitlock can get the entire fuck outta here. https://t.co/2jEYmY7Sei;[('Whitlock', 'PERSON')]
909815867742896128;2017-09-18 16:26:21;Staten Island, NY;40.6276964;-74.1620794;We're #hiring! Read about our latest #job opening here: Full Time Delivery Load Puller - https://t.co/11XNlzap9X #Labor NY #CareerArc;[('Full', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Time', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Delivery', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Load', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Puller', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815880242143233;2017-09-18 16:26:24;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@Tabelisnotabel We've got Russian bots, now we've got athletes with fake accounts. Is twitter even real?;[('Russian', 'MISC')]
909815886273380352;2017-09-18 16:26:25;Manhattan, NY;40.75863537;-73.98510933;New York #rainy #morning - photo by @lueurphoto . .  #crowd #human #people #street… https://t.co/XQG97xHwwb;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909815896331505667;2017-09-18 16:26:27;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;"@gayporngossip Why does a former #gayporn actor have ""Little Respect (If Any) 4 Porn Actors, Especially Black Ones""?https://t.co/NMmD8VtuVn";[('Little', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Respect', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Porn', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Actors', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Especially', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Black', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ones', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815897845489664;2017-09-18 16:26:28;Bethpage, NY;40.7374528;-73.4740979;We're #hiring! Click to apply: Drywall Installer - https://t.co/MFVtowLt37 #Construction #Farmingdale, NY #Job #Jobs #CareerArc;[('Drywall', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Installer', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815904288088064;2017-09-18 16:26:29;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Wow, was totally wondering where all of my 96 billion dollars went https://t.co/svQ3IBpaFm;[('Wow', 'PERSON')]
909815906209091584;2017-09-18 16:26:30;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@rking_19 2/Tactics discussed in my book: The Managed Healthcare Industry-Market  Failure, Hw Healthcare Becme Weal… https://t.co/gSioe1ufKj;[('Managed', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Healthcare', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Industry-Market', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Failure', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hw', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Healthcare', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Becme', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Weal', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815907073052672;2017-09-18 16:26:30;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;@hanyeseul_18 here's a birthday joke for you: Why did Tommy hit his birthday cake with a hammer? It was a Poundcake!;[('Tommy', 'PERSON')]
909815913150631936;2017-09-18 16:26:31;New York, NY;40.705597499999996;-73.977717;Elite NYC Escorts DATING, #International Escorts, Manhattan, #NYCESCORTS #ELITE #SEXY #VIP 646-575-4117… https://t.co/yQFf60qf5O;[('Elite', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DATING', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909815931949469697;2017-09-18 16:26:36;Manhattan, NY;40.77274259;-73.972216;So no one told you life was gonna be this wayyyy 👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼👏🏼 @ Central Park https://t.co/uuAGlPzBgw;[('Central', 'LOCATION'), ('Park', 'LOCATION')]
909815936118427648;2017-09-18 16:26:37;Manhattan, NY;40.75839;-73.98644;New collection- Young Reds 79 All sizes - Ships to USA & Europe free  Handmade in Italy… https://t.co/LJqNwCydk7;[('Young', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Reds', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('Europe', 'LOCATION'), ('Handmade', 'LOCATION'), ('Italy', 'LOCATION')]
909815961183772672;2017-09-18 16:26:43;Elizabeth, NJ;40.64644203;-74.2047731;Best offer 2008 Nissan Rogue SL AWD 2.5 V4 Fully loaded  Clean Title 1 owner alert just came hot… https://t.co/vL0sG0fP0D;[('Best', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nissan', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Rogue', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SL', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('AWD', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Clean', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Title', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815965432598529;2017-09-18 16:26:44;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;@Karachi_Post They are so blind they said even if Nawaz Sharif asked them to vote for a dog they would vote for the… https://t.co/Ybnod33GnL;[('Nawaz', 'PERSON'), ('Sharif', 'PERSON')]
909815966896357376;2017-09-18 16:26:44;Bloomingdale, NJ;41.022067500000006;-74.331649;I'm never getting over the fact that I wasn't paying attention and almost bumped into David Mazouz;[('David', 'PERSON'), ('Mazouz', 'PERSON')]
909815970323189761;2017-09-18 16:26:45;Staten Island, NY;40.572376000000006;-74.153947;To rank the Star Wars Movies worst to best: 1 5 2 3 4 6;[('Star', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Wars', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Movies', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815970415353856;2017-09-18 16:26:45;Syosset, NY;40.8262101;-73.502068;We're #hiring! Click to apply: CDL, Route Delivery Driver - https://t.co/HsKguMAjn6 #SupplyChain #Syosset, NY #Job #Jobs #CareerArc;[('CDL', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909815969769455616;2017-09-18 16:26:45;Jersey City, NJ;40.7180015;-74.066663;And we need problem again we finish having problems with Irma the Caribbean is in trouble again ok peace out sign G… https://t.co/nvWPYekhBV;[('Irma', 'PERSON'), ('Caribbean', 'LOCATION')]
909815975947767809;2017-09-18 16:26:46;Queens, NY;40.737648;-73.852134;Updated: Incident on #Q58Bus Both directions from 108th Street & Horace Harding Expressway to Horace Harding...https://t.co/r1c3eaadrE;[('Horace', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Harding', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Expressway', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Horace', 'PERSON'), ('Harding', 'PERSON')]
909815976732037121;2017-09-18 16:26:47;Queens, NY;40.701023;-73.841804;Updated: Incident on #Q55Bus Both directions from Myrtle Avenue : S Park Lane to Myrtle Avenue:Woodhaven Boulevard https://t.co/2dM2Y8dQ6k;[('Myrtle', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION'), ('Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lane', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Myrtle', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION'), ('Woodhaven', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Boulevard', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815977994571776;2017-09-18 16:26:47;Brooklyn, NY;40.714176;-73.931655;Updated: Incident on #Q54Bus WB at Metropolitan Bridge https://t.co/AN0Ah204p1;[('WB', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Metropolitan', 'LOCATION'), ('Bridge', 'LOCATION')]
909815978896367616;2017-09-18 16:26:47;Queens, NY;40.737648;-73.852134;Updated: Incident on #Q88Bus from 108th Street & Horace Harding Expressway to Horace Harding Expressway:College...https://t.co/r1c3eaadrE;[('Horace', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Harding', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Expressway', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Horace', 'PERSON'), ('Harding', 'PERSON')]
909815979701624832;2017-09-18 16:26:47;Brooklyn, NY;40.714176;-73.931655;Updated: Incident on #Q59Bus at Metropolitan Bridge https://t.co/AN0Ah204p1;[('Metropolitan', 'LOCATION'), ('Bridge', 'LOCATION')]
909815990103433216;2017-09-18 16:26:50;Massachusetts, USA;42.7070354;-71.1631137;See our latest #Lawrence, MA #job and click to apply: Store Team Member - https://t.co/J7ZRU1uznn #Labor #Hiring #CareerArc;[('MA', 'LOCATION'), ('Store', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Team', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Member', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815991382749184;2017-09-18 16:26:50;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;@JoshuaHorvath here's a birthday joke for you: How does Moby Dick celebrates his birthday? He has a whale of a party!;[('Moby', 'PERSON'), ('Dick', 'PERSON')]
909815992641101825;2017-09-18 16:26:50;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@Basketball3133 @NBA2K WTF!!! It corrupted my files again!!! I lost everything again!!! This game as it is... is un… https://t.co/zyE3fdZTIX;[('WTF', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909815991378612224;2017-09-18 16:26:50;New York, NY;40.705597499999996;-73.977717;"Must-see! ""Double Play"" is a coming of age story based in Curaçao. #doubleplaymovie #uw21 #urbanworldfilmfestival https://t.co/8BPsqFEGsD";[('Curaçao', 'LOCATION')]
909816005815398400;2017-09-18 16:26:54;BNP Paribas;40.762058;-73.981835;Very à propos. The @FrenchFounders Startup Tour final is about to start and @ovh has some great prizes for the winn… https://t.co/Yluh2PMBYQ;[('Startup', 'MISC'), ('Tour', 'MISC')]
909816007891570688;2017-09-18 16:26:54;Bronx, NY;40.85;-73.8667;Bronx Views 🌁 . . . #bx #bronx #ny #newyork #yankees #yankeestadium #theboogiedown… https://t.co/661SIahM9N;[('Bronx', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Views', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('🌁', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816017286725632;2017-09-18 16:26:56;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Sam Smith came out with his new music video and it's so beautiful 😭;[('Sam', 'PERSON'), ('Smith', 'PERSON')]
909816020105400320;2017-09-18 16:26:57;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;⚡️ “The Elf on the Shelf parodies are too much ”  https://t.co/NA8lvTEJf5;[('Elf', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816022215090176;2017-09-18 16:26:57;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;#Outnumbered  Let MSM keep on pushing Hillary. It just focuses people on the lack of policy on the side of the Dems.;[('MSM', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Dems', 'MISC')]
909816024601522176;2017-09-18 16:26:58;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Gonna see my bitch Bri tomorrow (':;[('Bri', 'PERSON')]
909816032570744832;2017-09-18 16:27:00;Fair Lawn, NJ;40.9389442;-74.1194526;Join the Panera Bread team! See our latest #job opening here: https://t.co/ZYpBvPm8rL #parttime #Hospitality #FairLawn, NJ #Veterans;[('Panera', 'LOCATION'), ('Bread', 'LOCATION'), ('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909816038107308032;2017-09-18 16:27:01;Clifton, NJ;40.859832;-74.1581305;IM IN LOOOOOOOVE 😍😩👅 https://t.co/2tVWEoRVDq;[('IM', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816049373204480;2017-09-18 16:27:04;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;I don't smoke weed, but if I ever smoked weed, I want whatever Kyrie Irving smoked before he went on First Take. WTF is he saying?;[('Kyrie', 'PERSON'), ('Irving', 'PERSON'), ('First', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Take', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('WTF', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816050446995456;2017-09-18 16:27:04;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;Just posted a photo @ New York, New York https://t.co/xrQKYG0Jje;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909816056247672833;2017-09-18 16:27:06;Staten Island, NY;40.572376000000006;-74.153947;It's time!!! Get to where you need to be- the Brooklyn Bridge at 3!! #spectrumstrike #local3 #UNIONSTRONG https://t.co/sOL5XPFjDL;[('Brooklyn', 'LOCATION'), ('Bridge', 'LOCATION')]
909816063617044482;2017-09-18 16:27:07;White Plains, NY;41.0262045;-73.754737;#PaceU roundtable discussion about DACA  https://t.co/FlDjCncKqb;[('DACA', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816069904199680;2017-09-18 16:27:09;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;Going to add Lithuania Denmark Ireland sweeden Russia Australia new zeland;[('Lithuania', 'LOCATION'), ('Denmark', 'LOCATION'), ('Ireland', 'LOCATION'), ('Russia', 'LOCATION'), ('Australia', 'LOCATION')]
909816070176952321;2017-09-18 16:27:09;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;"@GPTimes Why do I, a former #gayporn actor, have ""Little Respect (If Any) for #Porn Actors, Especially Black Ones""?https://t.co/NMmD8VtuVn";[('Little', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Respect', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Especially', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Black', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ones', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816075465875461;2017-09-18 16:27:10;Manhattan, NY;40.7127837;-74.0059413;Want to work at Starbucks? We're #hiring in #NewYork, NY! Click for details: https://t.co/nOIzb4IixK #CustomerService #Veterans #Job #Jobs;[('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909816082013270016;2017-09-18 16:27:12;Elizabeth, NJ;40.6622;-74.2091;Best offer 2008 Nissan Rogue SL AWD 2.5 V4 Fully loaded  Clean Title 1 owner alert just came hot… https://t.co/nemHKjgd46;[('Best', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nissan', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Rogue', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SL', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('AWD', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Clean', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Title', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816084957499392;2017-09-18 16:27:12;Manhattan, NY;40.7127837;-74.0059413;Want to work at Sanofi US? We're #hiring in #NewYork, New York! Click for details: https://t.co/oafdjJHHMh #Pharmaceutical #Job #Jobs;[('Sanofi', 'LOCATION'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909816083556835333;2017-09-18 16:27:12;New York, NY;40.705597499999996;-73.977717;@sternbergh @NaomiAKlein Sir Patrick could do it better! https://t.co/9crp7snrIN;[('Patrick', 'PERSON')]
909816091714707456;2017-09-18 16:27:14;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;Elite NYC Escorts DATING, #International Escorts, Manhattan, #NYCESCORTS #ELITE #SEXY #VIP 646-575-4117… https://t.co/g0GWEZibiC;[('Elite', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DATING', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909816097544851458;2017-09-18 16:27:15;Stamford, CT;41.0983345;-73.554097;Breaking news slate CBS Baltimore https://t.co/XysV1zvy0F;[('CBS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Baltimore', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816110710706177;2017-09-18 16:27:19;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Italy has some of the best coffee shops and brands in the world. Starbucks has no business in Italy. https://t.co/F6oblT29Cs;[('Italy', 'LOCATION'), ('Starbucks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Italy', 'LOCATION')]
909816130784591872;2017-09-18 16:27:23;Fort Lee, NJ;40.848333499999995;-73.972455;I'm not Vegan because I don't wanna kill animals, I'm vegan because I don't wanna kill myself..... 👌🏼;[('Vegan', 'LOCATION')]
909816131095015424;2017-09-18 16:27:23;Queens, NY;40.76313279;-73.77178826;I'm at LIRR - Bayside Station - @lirrdeals4u in Bayside, NY https://t.co/SZkMeVYUq6;[('LIRR', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bayside', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Station', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bayside', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909816131799666688;2017-09-18 16:27:24;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;A sex-segregated bus in Brooklyn. https://t.co/Ch6Jw9z0ih;[('Brooklyn', 'LOCATION')]
909816152888627206;2017-09-18 16:27:29;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;@DitadeLeon here's a birthday joke for you: How does Darth Vader know Luke Skywalker got him for his birthday? He felt his presents!;[('Darth', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Vader', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Luke', 'PERSON'), ('Skywalker', 'PERSON')]
909816157712023554;2017-09-18 16:27:30;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Sweatpants & Soul | The First Shower After https://t.co/C2AyJOAMcD @SweatpantsCafe;[('Sweatpants', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Soul', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816169309368320;2017-09-18 16:27:32;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;Donald Trump AKA POTUS is only loyal to SELF WHOM HE TALKS TO DAILY 😜;[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('AKA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('POTUS', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816177341460481;2017-09-18 16:27:34;Parsippany, NJ;40.8565465;-74.44141850000001;@Marvel @twhiddleston @Thomas100273  I can't wait for that meeting with Hulk.;[('Hulk', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816179551850496;2017-09-18 16:27:35;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;New York #rainy #morning - photo by @lueurphoto . .  #crowd #human #people #street… https://t.co/ZAtsIiw39I;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909816194517147649;2017-09-18 16:27:38;Bethpage, NY;40.7442664;-73.4820687;This #job might be a great fit for you: Field Service Technician - Bethpage, New York - https://t.co/TqQ99oiRhD #SkilledTrade #Bethpage, NY;[('Field', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Service', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Technician', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bethpage', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909816206563135488;2017-09-18 16:27:41;MTA Subway - 23rd St (F/M);40.7429;-73.992791;Nice. They just started Subway time at 23rd and Sixth Avenue https://t.co/gtfcEdoANr;[('Nice', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816207624359937;2017-09-18 16:27:42;Elizabeth, NJ;40.64644203;-74.2047731;Best offer 2008 Nissan Rogue SL AWD 2.5 V4 Fully loaded  Clean Title 1 owner alert just came hot… https://t.co/UGtJD4eNYc;[('Best', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nissan', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Rogue', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SL', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('AWD', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Clean', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Title', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816218785329152;2017-09-18 16:27:44;Jersey City, NJ;40.7180015;-74.066663;YASS DNA IS TRENDING #1 ON YOUTUBE! IM LIVING!   #BTS_DNA_TODAY https://t.co/gREglH8BJo;[('YASS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DNA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('IM', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816225362010112;2017-09-18 16:27:46;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@jay4Toya Me? Omg. Just twitter search for my handle and taylor, swift, taylor swift, t swift;[('Omg', 'LOCATION')]
909816228377694208;2017-09-18 16:27:47;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Just to take mani to see Cardi b and migos she'll lose her damn mind;[('Cardi', 'PERSON')]
909816230688825345;2017-09-18 16:27:47;Elmsford, NY;41.053224;-73.8164115;Bagpipe serenade at Knollwood. https://t.co/3Pgh41qlc3;[('Knollwood', 'LOCATION')]
909816248925659136;2017-09-18 16:27:51;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;I think I am just going to try to take it easy. I am leaving my notifications off for Twitter & Facebook though.;[('Twitter', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Facebook', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816252884975616;2017-09-18 16:27:52;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;Just posted a photo @ New York, New York https://t.co/2M9yfg8Ssa;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909816252658356234;2017-09-18 16:27:52;Manhattan, NY;40.7127837;-74.0059413;Join the United Staffing Solutions team! See our latest #job opening here: https://t.co/oiHgaIkKJH #Clerical #NewYork, NY #Hiring;[('United', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Staffing', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Solutions', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909816253413511168;2017-09-18 16:27:53;New York, NY;40.705597499999996;-73.977717;Elite NYC Escorts DATING, #International Escorts, Manhattan, #NYCESCORTS #ELITE #SEXY #VIP 646-575-4117… https://t.co/wbLQQdI25x;[('Elite', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DATING', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Escorts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909816255850401792;2017-09-18 16:27:53;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;I can't wait to write everything I just learned about Zach and his life.;[('Zach', 'PERSON')]
909816263458910208;2017-09-18 16:27:55;Great Neck Plaza, NY;40.78657478;-73.72878557;I'm at LIRR- Port Washington Line in Queens, NY https://t.co/eFFsYOeyff;[('LIRR', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Port', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Washington', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Line', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Queens', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909816266382290947;2017-09-18 16:27:56;Queens, NY;40.707176;-73.789901;Updated: Incident on #Q54Bus from 170th Street:Jamaica Avenue to Jamaica Avenue:Van Wyck Expressway https://t.co/lfcmrV8r2y;[('Jamaica', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION'), ('Jamaica', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION'), ('Van', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Wyck', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Expressway', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816267250466816;2017-09-18 16:27:56;Queens, NY;40.707176;-73.789901;Updated: Incident on #Q56Bus from 170th Street:Jamaica Avenue to Jamaica Avenue:Van Wyck Expressway https://t.co/lfcmrV8r2y;[('Jamaica', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION'), ('Jamaica', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION'), ('Van', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Wyck', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Expressway', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816273281921024;2017-09-18 16:27:57;West Caldwell, NJ;40.846404;-74.2946025;@ERtheII Don't you dare, Noel woulda been way cheaper and had the same production 😢😢😢;[('Noel', 'PERSON')]
909816280047325184;2017-09-18 16:27:59;Clifton, NJ;40.859832;-74.1581305;The Rare, Potent Fuel Powering North Korea’s Weapons https://t.co/tT2MeL1AtV Cut off the fuel,cut of the snake.Find other item critical cut.;[('Potent', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fuel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Powering', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('North', 'LOCATION'), ('Korea', 'LOCATION')]
909816289962680320;2017-09-18 16:28:01;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;At UN High Level Meeting on Hurricane Irma response, @UNOCHA Dir. cites UN capacity already in position to respond to the next storm.;[('UN', 'LOCATION'), ('Irma', 'PERSON'), ('Dir', 'LOCATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816294869958656;2017-09-18 16:28:02;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;If you like Tyrod more than EJ i don't even wanna talk to you about the bills just get out of my face before I start dropping knowledge;[('Tyrod', 'PERSON')]
909816301874491392;2017-09-18 16:28:04;New York, USA;43.3358;-78.0761;"Re-post @bahsanford Next song I'm dropping 💑🇯🇲 🎶 💘 ""Best Friend"" Prod. by… https://t.co/A5H1iqA7gL";[('Best', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Friend', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816302491066368;2017-09-18 16:28:04;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;"Greg Olsen was out and I thought ""no big deal I have Eifert"". I should know better.";[('Greg', 'PERSON'), ('Olsen', 'PERSON'), ('Eifert', 'PERSON')]
909816305615867905;2017-09-18 16:28:05;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;"@Fleshbot Why do I, a former #gayporn actor, have ""Little Respect (If Any) For #Porn Actors, Especially Black Ones""? https://t.co/NMmD8VtuVn";[('Little', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Respect', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Especially', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Black', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ones', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816306119041026;2017-09-18 16:28:05;Manhattan, NY;40.7581;-73.9869;Hello Toddy! Things got weird at the #ShubertTheatre & apparently I'm a talking head now.… https://t.co/hqOYGhvGW2;[('Hello', 'PERSON'), ('Toddy', 'PERSON')]
909816312142147584;2017-09-18 16:28:07;New York, NY;40.705597499999996;-73.977717;Cities are frontline players in dealing with refugees: UNHCR ready to step up its engagement with Mayors around the… https://t.co/gN6U56OU9h;[('UNHCR', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Mayors', 'MISC')]
909816317137625088;2017-09-18 16:28:08;Baldwin Harbor, NY;40.6319905;-73.602047;Five attorneys on Russian probe contribute to Hillary Clinton's campaign and are Democrats always smell la rotten egg like Comey;"[('Russian', 'MISC'), ('Hillary', 'PERSON'), (""Clinton's"", 'PERSON'), ('Democrats', 'MISC'), ('Comey', 'PERSON')]"
909816317406056448;2017-09-18 16:28:08;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;"""Too many Instagram models""";[('Instagram', 'MISC')]
909816323143806976;2017-09-18 16:28:09;Massachusetts, USA;42.036939000000004;-71.683502;@RealJamesWoods We Didn't See You At #Emmys James ! We Do Have The Highest Honor & Respect For You! 🌟👍🇺🇸 https://t.co/iLh0wd9Pt6;[('James', 'PERSON'), ('Highest', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Honor', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Respect', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('For', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('You', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816337223974918;2017-09-18 16:28:13;Stamford, CT;41.0983345;-73.554097;@OnePlus_IN I hope i will get a Karbon case at least for my #OnePlus5 #10DaysofGiveaways;[('Karbon', 'PERSON')]
909816347508568065;2017-09-18 16:28:15;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Spotted outside the UN. #UNGA https://t.co/kGPBwf2iBH;[('UN', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816354785636359;2017-09-18 16:28:17;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Holocaust Centers. Never forget. https://t.co/S8GlbYc6NW;[('Holocaust', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Centers', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816359848222720;2017-09-18 16:28:18;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@stillwilderness Hey Lance sorry to hear that, what shop did you stop by? We'd love to offer a full refund of the p… https://t.co/oC6N3vOZ2Q;[('Hey', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lance', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816369268625410;2017-09-18 16:28:20;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Happy to speak @ClimateGroup #CWNYC and share how @Aurubis_AG help decarbonize Hamburg with CO2 neutral heat… https://t.co/d1XDWT5kKc;[('Hamburg', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816378617712640;2017-09-18 16:28:22;Old Westbury, NY;40.786978;-73.595206;Trynna figure out why J.R Smith would be in this picture... https://t.co/B0UvlZK8nr;[('Trynna', 'PERSON'), ('Smith', 'PERSON')]
909816384812707841;2017-09-18 16:28:24;Dobbs Ferry, NY;41.011495999999994;-73.8644785;Amell Named ECAC Division II Field Hockey League Defensive Player of the Week @PeteRuf12 @lohudsports @ECACDIIFH https://t.co/M5PaTMnFLR;[('Amell', 'MISC'), ('Named', 'MISC'), ('ECAC', 'MISC'), ('Division', 'MISC'), ('II', 'MISC'), ('Field', 'MISC'), ('Hockey', 'MISC'), ('League', 'MISC'), ('Defensive', 'MISC'), ('Player', 'MISC')]
909816407990390784;2017-09-18 16:28:29;Pace University;40.711109;-74.005044;Motivational mantra Monday #paasa #educate2eliminate #staypositive https://t.co/RSmSLjRjsv;[('Motivational', 'MISC')]
909816410070585344;2017-09-18 16:28:30;Edison, NJ;40.5230137;-74.3411515;Want to work at UPS? We're #hiring in #Edison, NJ! Click for details: https://t.co/kjmNJhPtNY #Engineering #Job #Jobs #CareerArc;[('UPS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909816412146774016;2017-09-18 16:28:30;Valley Stream, NY;40.6642699;-73.7084645;We're #hiring! Read about our latest #job opening here: Shift Supervisor Management Trainee - https://t.co/G4v2krkUmr #Labor #CareerArc;[('Shift', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Supervisor', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Management', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trainee', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816412411015169;2017-09-18 16:28:30;Secaucus, NJ;40.7895453;-74.0565298;If you're looking for work in #Secaucus, NJ, check out this #job: https://t.co/rNnPsAmxnz #Nursing #Hiring #CareerArc;[('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909816414080585731;2017-09-18 16:28:31;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;I opened a word dim Tennyson for Ming striking for rem armor and for phan out the bible destryed jgn;[('Tennyson', 'LOCATION')]
909816415506407424;2017-09-18 16:28:31;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;@TeamCavuto BEN CARSON'S VALUES & PRINCIPLES CONFUSE U. U ONLY RELATE WHEN PERSONALLY ELEVATED TO A HIGHER STANDARD? NOT IMPRESSIVE.;[('BEN', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816415938646016;2017-09-18 16:28:31;Manhattan, NY;40.75177656;-74.00636836;You're invited to Business, Design, Technology Conference (@bdtconference) 2017 presented by… https://t.co/GQjg2lUvig;[('Design', 'PERSON')]
909816423828082688;2017-09-18 16:28:33;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Joseph Goebbels took an epic celeb selfie at the emmys and it's all the feels;[('Joseph', 'PERSON'), ('Goebbels', 'PERSON')]
909816429037400064;2017-09-18 16:28:34;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;You live and you learn. 💙 @ New York, New York https://t.co/takE5Imaur;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909816467029397505;2017-09-18 16:28:43;East Rutherford, NJ;40.821188500000005;-74.0910375;Robby and @Ceswizzell get into heat debate 🔥🔥over Raiders 45 Jets 20 #NYJvsOAK https://t.co/WmqNGhpGBB https://t.co/WfWpVMUbWm;[('Robby', 'PERSON'), ('Raiders', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Jets', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816471718637568;2017-09-18 16:28:45;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;YO WHENS @softglas ALBUM COME OUT?;[('YO', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('WHENS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('ALBUM', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816478920331264;2017-09-18 16:28:46;United Nations;40.749224;-73.968673;Photo-Op w/ & UN Secretary-General & Hassan Rouhani, President, Islamic Republic of Iran at the United Nations in N… https://t.co/LvOM5nXuP0;[('Photo-Op', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hassan', 'PERSON'), ('Rouhani', 'PERSON'), ('Islamic', 'LOCATION'), ('Republic', 'LOCATION'), ('of', 'LOCATION'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('United', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nations', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816491654156288;2017-09-18 16:28:49;Brooklyn, NY;40.615644;-74.031186;Construction on #RLine Both directions from Bay Ridge-95th Street Station to 36th Street Station https://t.co/bd8nUE2vLB;[('Bay', 'LOCATION'), ('Ridge', 'LOCATION')]
909816491582910464;2017-09-18 16:28:49;Brooklyn, NY;40.615644;-74.031186;Construction on #RLine Both directions from Bay Ridge-95th Street Station to 36th Street Station https://t.co/tXIV93xCoS;[('Bay', 'LOCATION'), ('Ridge', 'LOCATION')]
909816494665715714;2017-09-18 16:28:50;Queens, NY;40.749534;-73.938301;Updated: Incident on #VariousBus Both directions at Queens Boulevard:Queens Plaza E https://t.co/ryirwWQg7q;[('Queens', 'LOCATION'), ('Boulevard', 'LOCATION'), ('Queens', 'LOCATION'), ('Plaza', 'LOCATION')]
909816495814914054;2017-09-18 16:28:50;Queens, NY;40.745241;-73.90666;Updated: Construction on #Q18Bus Both directions at 58th Street: Roosevelt Avenue https://t.co/IsGl8seXw1;[('Roosevelt', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION')]
909816496746004480;2017-09-18 16:28:51;Fort Lee, NJ;40.853282;-73.960134;Updated: Construction on #GeorgeWashingtonBridge EB from New Jersey Side/Lower Level to New York Side/Lower Level https://t.co/i7ZpP8BbFP;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('Jersey', 'LOCATION'), ('Side', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('Side', 'LOCATION')]
909816498725818368;2017-09-18 16:28:51;Queens, NY;40.749534;-73.938301;Updated: Incident on #QueensBus at Queens Boulevard:Queens Plaza E https://t.co/ryirwWQg7q;[('Queens', 'LOCATION'), ('Boulevard', 'LOCATION'), ('Queens', 'LOCATION'), ('Plaza', 'LOCATION')]
909816499937964032;2017-09-18 16:28:51;Queens, NY;40.749534;-73.938301;Updated: Incident on #LocalBus at Queens Boulevard:Queens Plaza E https://t.co/ryirwWQg7q;[('Queens', 'LOCATION'), ('Boulevard', 'LOCATION'), ('Queens', 'LOCATION'), ('Plaza', 'LOCATION')]
909816501208862720;2017-09-18 16:28:52;Queens, NY;40.749534;-73.938301;Updated: Incident on #ExpressBus at Queens Boulevard:Queens Plaza E https://t.co/ryirwWQg7q;[('Queens', 'LOCATION'), ('Boulevard', 'LOCATION'), ('Queens', 'LOCATION'), ('Plaza', 'LOCATION')]
909816507663896576;2017-09-18 16:28:53;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;Here’s a song for you… The Needle And The Damage Done by Neil Young https://t.co/3McdLN335A;[('Needle', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('And', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('The', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Damage', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Done', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Neil', 'PERSON'), ('Young', 'PERSON')]
909816509169532928;2017-09-18 16:28:54;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;I wonder if Hollywood realizes that Melissa McCarthy and Sean Spicer are actually 2 different people. One is comedy… https://t.co/0B601QjABJ;[('Hollywood', 'LOCATION'), ('Melissa', 'PERSON'), ('McCarthy', 'PERSON'), ('Sean', 'PERSON'), ('Spicer', 'PERSON')]
909816511640084480;2017-09-18 16:28:54;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;#Outnumbered  Hillary is still given a platform that she uses to bash Trump and further divide the country. Irresponsible and dangerous;[('Hillary', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]
909816530795458561;2017-09-18 16:28:59;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;Talking about I'm supporting a fake bitch..Wtf is lil Kim then, the bitch don't even like herself getting 50 surgeries bitch bye 😂😴;[('Wtf', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Kim', 'PERSON')]
909816539330772994;2017-09-18 16:29:01;Port Washington, NY;40.829604;-73.6823705;BIG two days for @CanesHoops. Jim Larrañaga is seeing wing Nassir Little (@2ez_nassie) today & guard Jalen Carey (@yungswae5) tomorrow.;[('Jim', 'PERSON'), ('Larrañaga', 'PERSON'), ('Nassir', 'PERSON'), ('Little', 'PERSON'), ('Jalen', 'PERSON'), ('Carey', 'PERSON')]
909816548067553282;2017-09-18 16:29:03;Yonkers, NY;40.944567500000005;-73.86085700000001;@iamhamesh Blair/Brown 2020: You fucks ruined the country while we were gone. Now we're coming back to make it great again.;[('Blair', 'PERSON'), ('Brown', 'LOCATION')]
909816546398232576;2017-09-18 16:29:02;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Supreme proxies available now for this week -- residential, $1 per w minimum order of 10 -- DM to order. https://t.co/XkwWywlLll;[('DM', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816561317314561;2017-09-18 16:29:06;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;He has season tickets in section 538 to watch the Mets. He's been through a lot this year. https://t.co/PM2XdzwWjn;[('Mets', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816572528783363;2017-09-18 16:29:09;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;New Orleans Saints coach Sean Payton told NFL Network Sunday that using Peterson the way he was used by the Vikings was never discussed.;[('Orleans', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Saints', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sean', 'PERSON'), ('Payton', 'PERSON'), ('NFL', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Peterson', 'PERSON'), ('Vikings', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816585917026304;2017-09-18 16:29:12;Livingston, NJ;40.7880615;-74.328959;"Scott Wheres the money your ""PAC"" collected? Tweeting lies about Trump don't count!  @RealJamesWoods @WillCaskey… https://t.co/NKUypWY0Rs";[('Scott', 'PERSON'), ('Wheres', 'PERSON'), ('PAC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]
909816608637505537;2017-09-18 16:29:17;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;.@Kevinliptakcnn dug up this photo of the last time Trump was at the UN -- back in 2000 https://t.co/0PP4GKZdgw;[('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816623258796038;2017-09-18 16:29:21;Massachusetts, USA;42.036939000000004;-71.683502;anyone around Plymouth want to grab food??;[('Plymouth', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816634503811072;2017-09-18 16:29:23;Connecticut, USA;41.500753;-72.757385;HOME TODAY: Girls Soccer, North Haven 3:45pm, Girls Volleyball, Wilbur Cross, 5:15pm Come Support!! GO SPARTANS! #AR5 #ctgsoc #ctvb;[('North', 'LOCATION'), ('Haven', 'LOCATION'), ('Girls', 'LOCATION'), ('Volleyball', 'LOCATION'), ('Wilbur', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Cross', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SPARTANS', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816645924814849;2017-09-18 16:29:26;Yonkers, NY;40.944567500000005;-73.86085700000001;@iamhamesh This time, we have spiffy Ads made by Wieden Kennedy. Weez are unstoppable!;[('Wieden', 'PERSON'), ('Kennedy', 'PERSON')]
909816646734422018;2017-09-18 16:29:26;Little Falls, NJ;40.86553383;-74.19835916;Time to drop the puck on a new season. #goblues #ponytail #likeagirl @ Floyd Hall Arena https://t.co/9L6BZmdddM;[('Floyd', 'LOCATION'), ('Hall', 'LOCATION'), ('Arena', 'LOCATION')]
909816666367909890;2017-09-18 16:29:31;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Not only do I get to see my pops today, but my older sister took a trip to Maryland and is spending her last two days with me in NY 😊😊😊😊;[('Maryland', 'LOCATION')]
909816668729290752;2017-09-18 16:29:32;Roselle, NJ;40.650436;-74.2596685;@foxnation The middle class, never left !  Just typical  Fake News !;[('Fake', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('News', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816697250619395;2017-09-18 16:29:38;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;Tried to bribe my Lyft driver to not pick up anyone else on the way from the airport. He didn't accept. Now I'm in traffic GODDAMIT.;[('Lyft', 'LOCATION')]
909816719820181506;2017-09-18 16:29:44;Northvale, NJ;41.009222;-73.951927;BK nuggets>>>>>Mcdonald's nuggets;[('BK', 'LOCATION')]
909816722403872769;2017-09-18 16:29:44;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Lucien Zayan, Founder of @TheInvisibleDog Art Center. https://t.co/V7RKrVM2zg https://t.co/p8nSi3zrFe;[('Lucien', 'PERSON'), ('Zayan', 'PERSON'), ('Art', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Center', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816726652690434;2017-09-18 16:29:45;Massapequa, NY;40.670076;-73.470948;On a happier note, The View's wingnut du jour Jedediah Bila is leaving The View.;[('Jedediah', 'PERSON'), ('Bila', 'PERSON'), ('View', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816729303384064;2017-09-18 16:29:46;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Genuine & Authentic, Love. That means the world to me. Love overcomes all hate and distraction. If you're not that type, your not my type.;[('Genuine', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Authentic', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Love', 'PERSON')]
909816736937074688;2017-09-18 16:29:48;New York, NY;40.705597499999996;-73.977717;Only a few more minutes before the @SPLENDA Twitter Party!  Who's joining me?#SplendaNaturals #Emmys #ad;[('Twitter', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Party', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816747414364160;2017-09-18 16:29:50;Manhattan, NY;40.7207559;-74.0007613;https://t.co/5BF8BDpoOu Watch the latest Zenspath Podcast with Caleb & Jeremy about the #NintendoDirect!;[('Zenspath', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Podcast', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Caleb', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Jeremy', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816748098154496;2017-09-18 16:29:50;Queens, NY;40.748992;-73.756607;Updated: Construction on #VariousBus Both directions from Springfield Boulevard:Horace Harding S to Springfield...https://t.co/2E6EzTFTLs;[('Springfield', 'LOCATION'), ('Boulevard', 'LOCATION'), ('Horace', 'PERSON'), ('Harding', 'PERSON'), ('Springfield', 'LOCATION')]
909816748823633921;2017-09-18 16:29:51;Manhattan, NY;40.7078;-74.0119;#Marvel #Mondays #iJustmadethatUp @ Lower Manhattan https://t.co/rj0pJ8WNMM;[('Manhattan', 'LOCATION')]
909816749058641922;2017-09-18 16:29:51;Queens, NY;40.748992;-73.756607;Updated: Incident on #QueensBus from Springfield Boulevard:Horace Harding S to Springfield Boulevard:56th Avenue https://t.co/2E6EzTFTLs;[('Springfield', 'LOCATION'), ('Boulevard', 'LOCATION'), ('Horace', 'PERSON'), ('Harding', 'PERSON'), ('Springfield', 'LOCATION'), ('Boulevard', 'LOCATION')]
909816755031281665;2017-09-18 16:29:52;Manhattan, NY;40.73962938;-74.00871149;View from above...#whitneymuseum #newyork #art @ Whitney Museum of… https://t.co/IZHfvdgXnE;[('Whitney', 'PERSON'), ('Museum', 'PERSON')]
909816755782127617;2017-09-18 16:29:52;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;I kinda live close to the UN. I'm about to get on Grindr and find me a prince;[('UN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Grindr', 'LOCATION')]
909816761117274114;2017-09-18 16:29:54;Paterson, NJ;40.915047;-74.16780750000001;Ima stay 💯..even when you don't 🤷🏼‍♀️;[('Ima', 'PERSON')]
909816777521188864;2017-09-18 16:29:57;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;.@AlexisLives my Liza pin fell off my bag and thank god my friend watched it happen or it would have been gone forever;[('Liza', 'LOCATION')]
909816784051519488;2017-09-18 16:29:59;Newark, NJ;40.735657;-74.1723667;Want to work at RWJBH? We're #hiring in #Newark, NJ! Click for details: https://t.co/YQKis4ZnLs #Nursing #Job #Jobs #CareerArc;[('RWJBH', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909816784123043841;2017-09-18 16:29:59;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@ggreenwald Obama is no Jimmy Carter.   Take that however you wish.;[('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('Jimmy', 'PERSON'), ('Carter', 'PERSON')]
909816784982642688;2017-09-18 16:29:59;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;At UN High Level Meeting on Hurricane Irma response, #Bahamas MFA cites high recovery costs from three devastating storms over three years.;[('UN', 'LOCATION'), ('Irma', 'PERSON'), ('MFA', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816786614460417;2017-09-18 16:30:00;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Top Notch Adult Entertainment Club https://t.co/UNchXv0VTs  2124708808 #Top #luxury #International #VIPs #Escorts h… https://t.co/Wo77MxzxYe;[('Notch', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Adult', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Entertainment', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816791924396033;2017-09-18 16:30:01;Manhattan, NY;40.75987811;-73.97975636;Dave Chapelle handing @donaldglover one of his two Emmy's reminded me of a show I'll never… https://t.co/IOkaFs4jxM;[('Dave', 'PERSON'), ('Chapelle', 'PERSON')]
909816789688885248;2017-09-18 16:30:00;Apple Store, Fifth Avenue;40.763823;-73.97301;5th Avenue Apple Store right now https://t.co/FKoa3Epl0v;[('Apple', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Store', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816795057582080;2017-09-18 16:30:02;Brooklyn, NY;40.5745379;-73.9690976;2017/09/23: Brooklyn, NY, United States: Coney Island Boadwalk Season Finale - The Real (Mu… https://t.co/k8nQ1tz6dM https://t.co/VkmoFZo5f5;[('Brooklyn', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION'), ('United', 'LOCATION'), ('States', 'LOCATION'), ('Coney', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Island', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Boadwalk', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Season', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Finale', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816795678351360;2017-09-18 16:30:02;Harrison, NY;41.0192955;-73.7192005;1479 patriots follow me! They follow me for the truth and the most up to date ground level Trump support! Real News First! Follow now here!;[('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('Real', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('News', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('First', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816797460807680;2017-09-18 16:30:02;East Hanover, NJ;40.8135401;-74.3646122;Want to work at JDHuntr In-House Jobs ? We're #hiring in #EastHanover, NJ! Click for details: https://t.co/DlrunIxboK #Legal #Job #Jobs;[('JDHuntr', 'LOCATION'), ('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909816812673564673;2017-09-18 16:30:06;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Welcome to the #CitizensVoices #UNGA twitter chat with the Citizen-Led Accountability Coalition… https://t.co/RurcyHhKAi;[('Citizen-Led', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Accountability', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Coalition', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816817610317824;2017-09-18 16:30:07;Bedford Hills, NY;41.2294574;-73.7090958;Central Waters Bourbon Barrel Scotch Ale (2017) on tap now. https://t.co/DRWWz7d0nO @CWBrewing #BeerMenus;[('Central', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Waters', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bourbon', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Barrel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Scotch', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ale', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816826179268609;2017-09-18 16:30:09;Newark, NJ;40.734494;-74.184848;Jersey. https://t.co/uqx2zH1NNF;[('Jersey', 'LOCATION')]
909816829765287937;2017-09-18 16:30:10;Manhattan, NY;40.7127837;-74.0059413;Join the Healthfirst team! See our latest #job opening here: https://t.co/Jx4OJC6olf #SHP #Entitlement #NewYork, NY #Hiring #CareerArc;[('Healthfirst', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909816831627669504;2017-09-18 16:30:10;SoHo, Manhattan;40.7235455;-74.00347550000001;@NaomiAKlein @willmenaker Naomi, go back on Chapo;[('Naomi', 'PERSON')]
909816833708085248;2017-09-18 16:30:11;Orange, NJ;40.770981500000005;-74.2367465;omw to Livingston mall;[('Livingston', 'PERSON')]
909816835146731520;2017-09-18 16:30:11;New Jersey, USA;40.073040500000005;-74.7243235;@aoscott He was instrumental in Joan Crawford's  career. And, as Bette and us all know, Joan had quite the Golden Globes!;"[('Joan', 'PERSON'), (""Crawford's"", 'PERSON'), ('Bette', 'PERSON'), ('Joan', 'PERSON'), ('Golden', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Globes', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
909816835725512704;2017-09-18 16:30:11;Livingston, NJ;40.7880615;-74.328959;"Scott Wheres the money your ""PAC"" collected? Tweeting lies about Trump doesn't count!  @RealJamesWoods @WillCaskey… https://t.co/w46fA0CLEo";[('Scott', 'PERSON'), ('Wheres', 'PERSON'), ('PAC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]
909816846668517376;2017-09-18 16:30:14;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;#newyork be ready for this weekend! Omnilife is bringing us loads of info! #health #cosmetics #business #trips Inbo… https://t.co/WugJtri6s1;[('Omnilife', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816854293737472;2017-09-18 16:30:16;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;JPMorgan Chase poached an executive from Amazon to help the bank improve the customer… https://t.co/B1Khchm9z3;[('JPMorgan', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chase', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Amazon', 'LOCATION')]
909816870001364992;2017-09-18 16:30:20;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;Okay Athens. Let me know which photo you want to hear the backstory about. I'll include some of your suggestions. https://t.co/DpENPJEv7r;[('Okay', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Athens', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816890507382790;2017-09-18 16:30:24;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;Eddie Anderson, here in CABIN IN THE SKY ('43) being sweetly serenaded by Ethel Waters. #EddieAndreson #botd… https://t.co/agGxEZuby8;[('Eddie', 'PERSON'), ('Anderson', 'PERSON'), ('Ethel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Waters', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816891744677890;2017-09-18 16:30:25;North Brunswick, NJ;40.4457045;-74.473067;"She'll always be ""Hanoi Jane"" & nothing more. https://t.co/pV3SGVTdrY";[('Hanoi', 'MISC'), ('Jane', 'MISC')]
909816892520574978;2017-09-18 16:30:25;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;Upstate New York: home of roadkill;[('Upstate', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909816896983146496;2017-09-18 16:30:26;Brooklyn, NY;40.715;-73.95162;Good hang with the incomparable Nick Zinner, pre-show at the King Woman concert - thank you… https://t.co/m5zOXrLELZ;[('Nick', 'PERSON'), ('Zinner', 'PERSON'), ('King', 'MISC'), ('Woman', 'MISC')]
909816900309446656;2017-09-18 16:30:27;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@GenFlynn Hey, Mike! If you haven't cut your deal w/Mueller yet, I'd get moving if I were you. The line is getting… https://t.co/9w5jg1mVX2;[('Hey', 'LOCATION'), ('Mike', 'PERSON'), ('Mueller', 'PERSON')]
909816903048290304;2017-09-18 16:30:27;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;When your DP posts a photo of your work, I'd say it's safe to put it on social media. Here is my… https://t.co/dnLgxU0O3m;[('DP', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816905078276096;2017-09-18 16:30:28;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Top Notch Adult Entertainment Club https://t.co/UNchXv0VTs  2124708808 #Top #luxury #International #VIPs #Escorts h… https://t.co/grLLttk2h2;[('Notch', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Adult', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Entertainment', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816920010035201;2017-09-18 16:30:31;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;@juaninQNS @TonyAvella As usual, when it comes to transportation Tony Avella always on the wrong side. Yelling at p… https://t.co/iBWMuqzRKz;[('Tony', 'PERSON'), ('Avella', 'PERSON')]
909816921251631104;2017-09-18 16:30:32;Bedford Hills, NY;41.2294574;-73.7090958;Central Waters Bourbon Barrel Scotch Ale (2017) growlers now available. https://t.co/DRWWz7d0nO @CWBrewing #BeerMenus;[('Central', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Waters', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bourbon', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Barrel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Scotch', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ale', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816924883824640;2017-09-18 16:30:33;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;@twistedmac11 Ending A Life Based On The Limited Knowledge Of Only A Person's Personal Situation Ignores The Potent… https://t.co/FoSeqvej7L;[('Limited', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Knowledge', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Of', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Only', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816925122813952;2017-09-18 16:30:33;Yonkers, NY;40.9312099;-73.8987469;See our latest #Yonkers, NY #job and click to apply: Store Team Member - https://t.co/OD8O8u8r1X #Labor #Hiring #CareerArc;[('Store', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Team', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Member', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816925798010880;2017-09-18 16:30:33;White Plains, NY;41.0339862;-73.7629097;Can you recommend anyone for this #job? One to One Aide-JAC White Plains Campus - https://t.co/nQLqB9QcV4 #Clerical #WhitePlains, NY;[('White', 'LOCATION'), ('Plains', 'LOCATION'), ('Campus', 'LOCATION')]
909816936913096706;2017-09-18 16:30:35;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Short promo video for my new VI NYC Edition album Heart of the City available here https://t.co/6UwA9QLcey & iTunes. https://t.co/8ac4E9xYnV;[('VI', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NYC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Edition', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('album', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Heart', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('of', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('the', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('City', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909816952130035714;2017-09-18 16:30:39;Elizabeth, NJ;40.662479;-74.19652450000001;@UglyGod Don’t change who you is man. Look @ Dicky. There’s room for rappers like you. We need less molly talking rappers and more of you.;[('Don', 'PERSON'), ('’', 'PERSON'), ('Dicky', 'PERSON')]
909816958635343872;2017-09-18 16:30:41;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;"On this day in 1937, ""Their Eyes Were Watching God"" was released   📚💯Read my post about Nora Zeale Hurston… https://t.co/wwg1k6PJWh";[('Their', 'MISC'), ('Eyes', 'MISC'), ('Were', 'MISC'), ('Watching', 'MISC'), ('God', 'MISC'), ('Nora', 'PERSON'), ('Zeale', 'PERSON'), ('Hurston', 'PERSON')]
909816983977328640;2017-09-18 16:30:47;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;If I'm a character in Silent Hill then yes.... https://t.co/t0VrTtk2Vx;[('Hill', 'PERSON')]
909816984887545856;2017-09-18 16:30:47;Clifton, NJ;40.859832;-74.1581305;Is Trump a White Supremacist? https://t.co/mpBfQOzL4w YES,#Trumpisaracist;[('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('White', 'LOCATION'), ('Supremacist', 'LOCATION')]
909816994962210816;2017-09-18 16:30:49;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Top Notch Adult Entertainment Club https://t.co/UNchXv0VTs  2124708808 #Top #luxury #International #VIPs #Escorts h… https://t.co/da9tgqdRDH;[('Notch', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Adult', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Entertainment', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817004810539008;2017-09-18 16:30:52;Newark, NJ;40.7352;-74.1849;Deez niggaz said I changed...so I changed wit em 🤷🏾‍♂️💯. #TENSION out EVERYWHERE. @ Newark, New… https://t.co/PV1hpZxBoC;[('Newark', 'LOCATION')]
909817007754838016;2017-09-18 16:30:52;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;I've never seen an Asian women with any type of dude outside her race except a dread. That's all it's either Asian or dread.;[('Asian', 'MISC'), ('Asian', 'MISC')]
909817011445932038;2017-09-18 16:30:53;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;@vinnycrack Been a long time since I've seen the Crypt Keeper, how you been dude?;[('Crypt', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Keeper', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817018253111296;2017-09-18 16:30:55;New York, NY;40.689167;-74.044444;#ladyliberty @ Statue Of Liberty, Liberty Island, New York City https://t.co/16ckcP8q1Q;[('Statue', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Of', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Liberty', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Liberty', 'LOCATION'), ('Island', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('City', 'LOCATION')]
909817023680729088;2017-09-18 16:30:56;Roselle, NJ;40.650436;-74.2596685;@googlemaps There are washrooms in India ?  Who knew ?🤡;[('India', 'LOCATION')]
909817029523329025;2017-09-18 16:30:58;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Lmao thats facts tho https://t.co/1NG6NtVXlj;[('Lmao', 'LOCATION')]
909817034489208832;2017-09-18 16:30:59;Manhattan, NY;40.7609682;-73.9780638;This #job might be a great fit for you: Comm'l Loan Admin III - Asset Based Lending- NY, NY or Bedford, NH - https://t.co/0vNFDed74S NY;"[(""Comm'l"", 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Loan', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Admin', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('III', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NY', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bedford', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NH', 'LOCATION')]"
909817039161843712;2017-09-18 16:31:00;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;My bro @ New York, New York https://t.co/It9ZVR2ixG;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909817039543468034;2017-09-18 16:31:00;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;#pow @ New York, New York https://t.co/xxPZd7zqqg;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909817039316959232;2017-09-18 16:31:00;Roseland, NJ;40.8206555;-74.2937594;We're #hiring! Read about our latest #job opening here: store manager - Roseland, NJ - https://t.co/OgufbbTMbo #BusinessMgmt #Roseland, NJ;[('Roseland', 'LOCATION'), ('NJ', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817047013576705;2017-09-18 16:31:02;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Omg 🤣 we ALL want an Xtina concert 😭 #WhereAreYouChristina https://t.co/3rq1zzghiG;[('Xtina', 'MISC')]
909817047739174912;2017-09-18 16:31:02;Orange, NJ;40.770981500000005;-74.2367465;Eniko cheat back sis.;[('Eniko', 'LOCATION')]
909817083566768129;2017-09-18 16:31:10;Belleville, NJ;40.7936744;-74.1500469;Want to work at McDonald's Corporation? We're #hiring in #Belleville, NJ! Click for details: https://t.co/TFm0VcGPxw #Hospitality #Job;[('NJ', 'LOCATION')]
909817087656329216;2017-09-18 16:31:11;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;"Join me tonight w/ my special guest Fred Hof of @AtlanticCouncil at @NYUCGA; RSVP here https://t.co/MyGfIcJm5L @WorldPolicy @ACmideast";[('Fred', 'PERSON'), ('Hof', 'PERSON')]
909817099379527680;2017-09-18 16:31:14;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;@georgesalazar Why don't you spring for your own damn Lyft, moneybags.;[('Lyft', 'LOCATION')]
909817105775808512;2017-09-18 16:31:16;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Twitter will miss him as much as it misses Milo https://t.co/jNikJuCzwz;[('Milo', 'PERSON')]
909817107101208578;2017-09-18 16:31:16;Massapequa, NY;40.670076;-73.470948;I sent all paperwork to @BMW @BMWUSA hoping that our issue in Freeport NY gets resolved ASAP... more than 2 months waiting on this.;[('Freeport', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817114013421568;2017-09-18 16:31:18;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;RT @cylanceinc Threat Spotlight: MAN1 Malware - The Last Crusade? https://t.co/IjwZLQTHJx #infosec #cybersecurity… https://t.co/btS9PhwjVt;[('RT', 'LOCATION'), ('Malware', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817115900878848;2017-09-18 16:31:18;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Gorgeous!!...and the Butterflies are beautiful ! 🦋 https://t.co/Cx5br6OUzp;[('Butterflies', 'MISC')]
909817117666693120;2017-09-18 16:31:19;Queens, NY;40.6708795;-73.8311875;@richsolarstone what a Tune Rich!! Take care and enjoy your week. https://t.co/1xGbrDKIDB;[('Tune', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Rich', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817120338464771;2017-09-18 16:31:19;Huntington, NY;40.87084;-73.42645;This beautiful forest green top and elastic tulle skirt are available at both the Sayville and… https://t.co/BvP7GqOVpH;[('Sayville', 'LOCATION')]
909817121588305925;2017-09-18 16:31:20;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Dear @SenatorCollins @lisamurkowski @SenJohnMcCain This rushed bill hurts Americans. You voted no before, please do so again #GrahamCassidy;[('Americans', 'MISC')]
909817129079382018;2017-09-18 16:31:21;Brooklyn, NY;40.655138;-73.9487755;WooOw u can't get me a waffle maker ? 😕 https://t.co/VwcPlzSRFt;[('WooOw', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817130031382528;2017-09-18 16:31:22;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Explaining my posts on the connection between David Dinkins and David Patterson. #Judges #ColorBlind;[('David', 'PERSON'), ('Dinkins', 'PERSON'), ('David', 'PERSON'), ('Patterson', 'PERSON')]
909817141393809408;2017-09-18 16:31:24;New York, USA;42.746617;-75.77004099999999;@_dcforthree happy birthday bro hope it's a good one, but UA is gonna beat Siena cause we're better 💜💛💜💛;[('UA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Siena', 'LOCATION')]
909817153599213571;2017-09-18 16:31:27;Connecticut, USA;41.500753;-72.757385;AWAY TODAY: Boys Soccer @ Branford, 6:30 pm Field Hockey @ Shelton 3:45 pm Girls Swimming & Diving @ Foran 3:45 pm GO SPARTANS! #AR5;[('Branford', 'LOCATION'), ('Shelton', 'PERSON'), ('Foran', 'PERSON'), ('SPARTANS', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817164860841984;2017-09-18 16:31:30;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;•Horoscope for Monday, September 18• Today's Waxing New 🌙 in ♍️ is very active. Mars & Mercury… https://t.co/asLuo9KiPt;[('•', 'MISC'), ('Horoscope', 'MISC'), ('Mars', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Mercury', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817169252192256;2017-09-18 16:31:31;Manhattan, NY;40.7127837;-74.0059413;This #job might be a great fit for you: Property & Casualty Insurance - Manager- NE - https://t.co/b87yyZtWTK #Consulting #NewYork, NY;[('Property', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Casualty', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Insurance', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NE', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817169579528192;2017-09-18 16:31:31;United Nations;40.749224;-73.968673;Photo-Op w/ UN Secretary-General & Hassan Rouhani, President, Islamic Republic of Iran at the United Nations in NYC… https://t.co/gWWl5dEwEF;[('Photo-Op', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hassan', 'PERSON'), ('Rouhani', 'PERSON'), ('Islamic', 'LOCATION'), ('Republic', 'LOCATION'), ('of', 'LOCATION'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('United', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nations', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817185144467456;2017-09-18 16:31:35;Manhattan, NY;40.7142;-74.0064;Power couple. 💃🏻 @_IrissTang @ New York, New York https://t.co/yI6sR1RpQY;[('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION')]
909817195445854208;2017-09-18 16:31:37;Bronx, NY;40.8503475;-73.8494415;@DitadeLeon here's a birthday joke for you: Why did Tommy hit his birthday cake with a hammer? It was a Poundcake!;[('Tommy', 'PERSON')]
909817200005042177;2017-09-18 16:31:38;New York, NY;40.705597499999996;-73.977717;Top Notch Adult Entertainment Club https://t.co/UNchXv0VTs  2124708808 #Top #luxury #International #VIPs #Escorts h… https://t.co/M7TJzXk3ce;[('Notch', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Adult', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Entertainment', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817207378644993;2017-09-18 16:31:40;Manhattan, NY;40.73485019;-74.00273597;Preschool biker gang? (@ West Village in New York, NY) https://t.co/4JXB8hjC2P https://t.co/awGHhnzqFz;[('West', 'LOCATION'), ('Village', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('NY', 'LOCATION')]
909817221496664066;2017-09-18 16:31:43;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;Bucs ☠️ - 0 MUFC 👹👹👹👹 - 1 - 0 FSU Still UNDEFEATED since week 1 FF 🏆🏆🏆 - 0 this weekend  Solid sports things happened;[('Bucs', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('MUFC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('FSU', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Still', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UNDEFEATED', 'ORGANIZATION')]
909817249309102085;2017-09-18 16:31:50;Bellerose, NY;40.724205;-73.71659299999999;@BillyRay5229 Reminds me of the pilot when she asks Monroe when he'll start taking her seriously, and episode 9 whe… https://t.co/HD0nzCY2fz;[('Monroe', 'PERSON')]
909817253159464961;2017-09-18 16:31:51;Manhattan, NY;40.756052;-73.987037;Construction on #1Line BothDir/BothDir from 42nd Street-Times Square Station to 72nd Street Station https://t.co/IXGvYl6zoC;[('Street-Times', 'LOCATION'), ('Square', 'LOCATION'), ('Station', 'LOCATION')]
909817253193031680;2017-09-18 16:31:51;Manhattan, NY;40.756052;-73.987037;Construction on #1Line BothDir/BothDir from 42nd Street-Times Square Station to 72nd Street Station https://t.co/aVebLc7tly;[('Street-Times', 'LOCATION'), ('Square', 'LOCATION'), ('Station', 'LOCATION')]
909817253373325314;2017-09-18 16:31:51;Manhattan, NY;40.756052;-73.987037;Construction on #1Line BothDir/BothDir from 42nd Street-Times Square Station to 72nd Street Station https://t.co/oZghdFydyD;[('Street-Times', 'LOCATION'), ('Square', 'LOCATION'), ('Station', 'LOCATION')]
909817254153506817;2017-09-18 16:31:51;Manhattan, NY;40.756052;-73.987037;Incident on #2Line from 42nd Street-Times Square Station to 72nd Street Station https://t.co/IXGvYl6zoC;[('Street-Times', 'LOCATION'), ('Square', 'LOCATION'), ('Station', 'LOCATION')]
909817254094700556;2017-09-18 16:31:51;Manhattan, NY;40.756052;-73.987037;Incident on #2Line from 42nd Street-Times Square Station to 72nd Street Station https://t.co/aVebLc7tly;[('Street-Times', 'LOCATION'), ('Square', 'LOCATION'), ('Station', 'LOCATION')]
909817254371627009;2017-09-18 16:31:51;Manhattan, NY;40.756052;-73.987037;Incident on #2Line from 42nd Street-Times Square Station to 72nd Street Station https://t.co/oZghdFydyD;[('Street-Times', 'LOCATION'), ('Square', 'LOCATION'), ('Station', 'LOCATION')]
909817255231463424;2017-09-18 16:31:51;Manhattan, NY;40.780709;-73.9685415;@Ryality Oh! Yes, Ahsoka is a togrunta! Both have the head-tails, though!;[('Ahsoka', 'PERSON')]
909817257018130432;2017-09-18 16:31:52;Manhattan, NY;40.778919;-73.960388;Updated: Construction on #M1Bus NB at Madison Avenue:E 83rd Street https://t.co/jQ4tsCb64Q;[('Madison', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION')]
909817257177559042;2017-09-18 16:31:52;Bronx, NY;40.836784;-73.886222;Updated: Incident on #BX36Bus WB at Vyse Avenue : E 174th Street https://t.co/SqIRRoJOhh;[('WB', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Vyse', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION')]
